Hi!
What's up?
Today's Sunday.
And I'm gonna play more Neuter.
Because this game, even though I have technically completed it, I feel like I've only scratched the surface.
So we're gonna be exploring as much as we can.
The Smug Goat!
I don't usually catch the livestreams, so I figure I'll give some subs away instead of subscribing myself.
Thank you so much, man.
I really appreciate that.
We get to have you, though.
Shout out to the VOD watchers!
I mean, it is more convenient, right?
You get to pause and fast-forward all you want, or repeat.
Thank you, Goat!
How you feeling?
I'm feeling great!
I actually accidentally opened the can before the stream.
I'm sorry, so I'm already drinking it.
Yeah, I should have waited.
But it is what it is.
Other than that, I'm fantastic.
How about you, Limonade?
How you doing?
Twitch integration time?
No, I don't think so.
Not yet.
If ever.
We'll have to see.
Karaki!
Hello, Oliver!
Happy to catch you live!
Thank you for the content you're giving us.
Hey, no problem!
Honestly, I'm just enjoying these games.
All I do is click a button and speak out loud.
You know?
But thank you so much for saying that.
I'm glad you're enjoying it.
You've gotten me through some tough times, so glad to support.
Oh, man.
I'm happy to help out whatever I can.
I'm glad you're finding some enjoyment out of these things.
At least enough to help you through those times.
Thank you!
I'm usually Vodwatcher, but I make it when I can.
Okay, so you're rid of both.
Best of both worlds.
No can!
Hahaha!
That crying face!
I'm a bit sore from long bike ride yesterday.
Oh, okay.
But that's the nice sore, though.
That's the sore you feel proud of, right?
It's like the good exhausted.
Is this gonna be a long stream?
I don't know.
I actually do have something a little later today, so it actually can't be too long.
But I will... I'll play as much as I can.
Mr. Beat, hello.
Yesterday I completed your Outer Wilds playthrough.
Fantastic game.
Awesome music and details.
Man, that game is indeed fantastic.
Kind of want to play it again in the future in VR.
Maybe many years when I've forgotten most of it.
Even though I feel like I will never forget it.
You know what I mean?
If you're just playing the game, then Noida's Twitch integration is the last thing you want.
Yeah, that's the... that's the impression I got as well.
Elevi.
Outer Wilds still getting mileage after all this time.
Dude, people are still watching that series.
The first video has over a hundred thousand views now.
I don't understand where all these people are coming from.
For some reason, that series just... I don't even know.
Got shown to so many people on YouTube.
Heh, God Leap.
I love your name.
Getting the first win in Noida kind of freed my brain from thinking about playing to win.
But I guess Oliver never needed an extra excuse to go explore.
Yeah.
I mean, today is gonna be the day where I just wander the land.
You know?
Noida is a place and I will mentally go there today and just wander the land.
But also, of course, discovered new spells and kill a bunch of enemies and all that stuff.
Obviously, you gotta get... you gotta get through the levels, right?
So get powerful first.
Definitely want to explore the surface more.
Because I wrote down some interesting stuff last time.
We found a researcher's note or whatever, right?
So there's stuff to do with that that I want to explore.
Will there ever be plans for Twitch integration?
It later on.
Maybe it's... you know?
I can't tell.
I can't say for certain.
Yeah, Outer Wilds is a game you can't play again, unfortunately.
It's not the same the second time.
Well, I guess no games are, right?
But still.
Hey, Antlers!
Thanks for subscribing, man.
Antlers 12.
Was that because the name Antlers was taken and you're like, Antlers 1.
Ah, shit, that's also taken.
Antler 1, too?
That's my... that's my guess.
Hey, sub-goal, yeah.
I don't understand how this sub-goal works.
I think it's automatically adjusting it, like, dynamically.
Like, I haven't put that goal in there.
That's something that is automatic, I think.
But that is insane.
210 subscribers.
Thank you, man.
Thank you.
Welcome.
Alright, let's see here.
Also, I need to connect the keyboard here, as always.
You know how it is.
You guys may think this is a running gag or anything, but it's not.
I'm serious, this is... There we go.
And then I need to turn off the music here.
I just want to get right in, man.
Dude, I've been missing this game!
I feel like I'm even more excited for it now, you know, than I was before.
It's crazy.
Alright, click this button, bump, there we go.
We're in the game.
Alright, so continue.
I think I just immediately started a new run and then I went out again afterwards.
Right.
Nala Games, which is also a spell.
I figured that out last time.
Oh man, 100 health back at the beginning.
What a time to be alive.
Hold on, can I actually dig with this?
No, okay.
Just testing.
If I can make a little ledge, that's enough, you know.
So I'm gonna go down here first.
I'm gonna take my sweet time now.
I have already completed the game, so I'm just gonna... I have nothing to prove anymore.
Well, I never did, but you know what I mean.
So basically the plan is to get powerful as fuck again and then I'm gonna go to the surface and other places and explore.
I may even explore the entirety of that spider lair, which scares the shit out of me, but I'll do it, damn it.
I will do it.
So I have... this is actually a great weapon.
I like this weapon a lot.
What's that?
Worm pheromone.
Oh shit, already on fire here.
I actually don't understand what just happened.
How did I catch fire?
I think someone threw a bomb or something.
Taken care of.
What's that?
Oil.
Don't want to stand in that.
Hemis!
Whoops!
Okay.
Kill all the Hemis.
Oh and dude, we gotta experiment with the whole angering the gods stuff.
Pheromone potion.
I have to remember there's rules with that.
I was lucky last time because I had that perk where the gods looked the other way, but that's not always the case.
This one produces a flame and that's whiskey.
Incredible.
Let's get up there.
I mean, what if I just drink all the whiskey?
Then there's nothing to set a flame, right?
Oh, I'm drunk already just by being in it?
Hmm.
I have an idea.
Bomb it.
That's the solution to everything.
Alcoholics cried out in unison.
That's the saw blade.
These things are dangerous.
They will actually hurt me, so I need to be careful with those.
It does 20 damage though.
That's wild.
I also want to find a real good digging wand this time and just start digging in random directions.
Weird.
Look at these things.
They don't destroy the chest, but that does.
Oh, what?
There's a wand and a gold thingy in here?
So double spell and a rock.
Shuffle?
No.
That's not bad, I guess.
But there's only six rocks to throw at a time and it's gonna throw two at a time.
Wait, what the hell?
There's another one down there?
What the hell is going on?
Let me make my way through.
Did I just destroy that?
Crap.
Damn!
Wait a minute, this is acid, right?
Yeah, it's acid.
It's not toxic sludge.
That is acid!
So I don't know what happened to that golden thing.
I think it went down here somewhere.
Oh wait, I see gold on there.
I kind of want that gold.
Thank you.
What's that?
Shiny?
Oh, it is right there!
It's right there!
Hold on, this is how you do it.
Watch.
Oink!
Oh, but it's gonna explode.
Let's not fall for that one again.
How many times was it?
Two.
What
if I use this on it?
That doesn't do anything?
Oh man, I have to... I have to do it like that?
Okay, next time it's gonna explode for sure.
What if I do this?
Whoa!
Blow that up.
Did money come out of it?
Okay, I hear a guy with a shotgun.
What's that?
Polymorphine.
Now give me this.
Now I can do it again.
So one, two, three... oopsie daisy.
Be careful.
I mean, we already have a lot of money.
This is a great start.
Honestly, this is fantastic.
And wait a minute, this doesn't dig, right?
No, unfortunately.
But I want to go up and grab that health above, you know?
Man, I can't wait to see what other perks are in this game.
Wait, there's a wand there?
Hello?
I'm gonna grab that.
If I can, it's sort of locked in.
I have one bomb.
I think I'm gonna use it.
I need to see what that wand is.
Dynamite!
Fuck yeah!
Which replaced that one.
Amazing.
Uh oh.
There we go.
I also need to replace my water soon.
Oh wait, it's actually still kind of full.
It's fine.
This thing is emitting flames.
Ah, let's not go that way.
Go around here.
Now I can get up top.
I've got the dynamite.
Unfortunately, it's shuffle, shuffle, no shuffle.
This time, I'm gonna only have no shuffle wands later on, man.
I hate the shuffle wands.
No good has ever come of that.
Nice.
And that's also 100 gold up here now.
Just a tablet.
Here we go.
Beautiful.
Thank you.
Now we go up.
Do I have some recoil when I do this?
Hey!
I think there... Oh yeah, there is a bit of recoil.
Dude, that's way easier.
I should have done that from the start.
That is much easier.
Now I know about all the recoil stuff.
Boink!
Your curiosity is rewarded.
See, that's such a random little interaction there.
That makes me think, what else is in this game, you know?
Like, if that is a thing, only God knows what else could be going on under my nose here.
Boop!
Doink!
Kind of want to... Come on.
No.
Yeah, fine.
Be that way.
Okay.
I want to roll it off the cliff.
Okay, 482 gold already.
Good start.
I can get in anywhere now.
Let's go this way.
I want to find health down here.
Health and money.
That's like the main concern for me in the beginning.
Finding hearts and finding that glitter.
This is always the same, I feel like.
Not much RNG in that place.
Whoops.
Let's be careful with those things, by the way.
Yeah, worth it.
There's a guy above me.
May I just kill him?
So slippery!
You know what I want to try?
If I find a really good digging wand, I'm just gonna try find a wall and just dig, as long as the game lets me.
You know, similar to the Minecraft style.
Where I was like, okay, let's just dig down until I can't dig anymore.
I'm gonna try that.
Like everywhere.
Oh, look at that!
Hahaha, lovely.
That's sand.
How do I get through this easily?
I just, I just blow it up.
That works.
Sort of.
That shall burn.
Let me help it along.
Oh, hello there.
Porta!
No, maybe from the other side.
Maybe that's easier.
Yeah, I think so.
Ah, shit, now the sand on both sides.
This is turning into a comedy.
Can I just... Yeah, there we go.
Beautiful.
Very good.
And there's a wand.
Ah, I'm gonna blow that up.
This is the best starter wand.
Change my mind.
Okay, guess I gotta go from the top.
Ah, let's do like this.
Yeah, that works.
Now that is toxic sludge.
Question, does that actually hurt me?
It does.
I wasn't quite sure, because as it does hurt me, toxic sludge is a little weird.
But if I pour water in here, watch.
It's reacting.
Mix it up.
And now we have water.
And now we can grab more water and get the wand.
Oh, that's a better version of what I have right now.
0.15, 0.47.
More slots.
Oh, that's not bad.
Yo, that's a sick wand, no?
I like it.
Fuck yeah, sick upgrade.
Very cool.
Can't get through here, because that's, I believe, steel, yeah.
Steelio.
That's probably how they say steel and finish.
Probably wrong about that.
Damn it.
Cut them all open.
Uh, I want to get through there as well.
Not bad.
Collapsed mines.
So what is the deal with this place?
I'm gonna try and explore the entirety of this sub area.
Oh, I thought you were dead, Bo.
I thought you were dead!
Oh my god, I just lost a bunch of HP to that guy.
That was stupid.
But I totally thought I killed him with that first hit.
For some reason, I assumed he was dead.
What's up here?
Look at how this is sort of half broken.
Okay.
Bunch of coal.
Oh, I only have 14 tea left.
How the hell did I use so much already?
I'm way too liberal with that.
Got to calm down.
Whoa.
I got plenty of money though.
That means rerolling perks.
Oh, there's something above me too.
Oh, it's that guy.
He's actually scary.
Dumbass.
Come here, I have a sick wand.
Wanna mess with me?
Sick.
That is definitely the hardest enemy in this first region, in the hemisphere.
Wait a minute.
This is the tree, look.
Wait, why can't I pass here?
Oh, this...
Oh, okay.
I see.
This route is sort of part of the foreground, whereas this is part of the background.
Uh, shit, how am I gonna do this?
That works.
Oh, wait, they're locked in here.
Do I even want to get in there though?
I do wonder what's... if I keep going up, you know, what happens then.
But this is...
Look at this fucking area.
Oh, wait, I have light.
Oh, it works.
Yes.
Show me.
What do we have?
Light it up for me, Rock.
Oh, god.
Yo, it doesn't stay lit.
Oh, no.
Yo, it goes deep.
Let's follow the rock.
Come on, come on, come on.
Up, up, up, up, up.
Damn.
Come on.
Why is the rock falling so slow, by the way?
Oh, it's gone.
Oh, no.
Bastard.
I'm sort of stuck here now.
Dang it.
Blow it.
There it is.
It reached the bottom.
Okay.
Very cool.
I have one of these left.
What?
Why would I get in there?
You know, that's kind of dumb.
Let's not do that.
What's that?
Excuse me.
That is levitation.
Not bad.
Toxic sludge with more levitation.
Oh, I guess that levitation was here.
And someone broke it.
Not me.
It wasn't me.
Oh, we've got a dude.
Oh, watch.
I have a sick wand.
Whoa.
Okay.
You're fast.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I know you're angry.
Calm down now.
That's toxic sludge.
That means we can do that.
Mix it up.
Now we have more water.
Oh, wait.
That's lava.
Don't want none of that.
Boink.
So much water.
Oh, nice.
Let's fucking go.
Uh, the best way to get in there is probably to do this.
Drain it.
That works.
Uh-oh, uh-oh.
Oh, no.
Tell me I can get through that.
Oh, that's unreal.
Um, saw blade through wood.
It's gotta work, right?
No?
Hmm.
Maybe the rock.
No, I don't want to try the rock.
This one, though.
That's the solution.
There we go.
Sick.
Great start.
I heard you.
Uh, that's a barrel there.
What do I have?
Pheromone potion and worm pheromone.
Hmm.
Acceleration.
I'll take that.
That is a good thing.
What's that?
Whiskey potion.
You know what?
Maybe I'll take it.
Fuck the worm.
No, fuck the pheromone for now.
Give me whiskey.
Whiskey potion.
I like that it's called whiskey potion and not just whiskey.
Oh, that wand already checked.
I have two non-shuffle and two shuffle wands.
That is pheromone.
Oh, easy.
I'm kind of low on HP.
Oh, nice.
There's a heart.
Love to see that.
But there's a bunch of lava.
Oh, that heart is fucked.
Uh, how do I... That's how we do it in Kansas.
They do lots of things in Kansas.
They also do a shuffle there.
In Kansas City.
At least that's what I've heard.
Go up here and then up here.
Let's kill this guy.
Dude, almost a thousand gold.
I don't think I've ever had this much in the first level.
Uh, toxic sludge.
That means that and then we mix.
Look.
Beautiful stuff.
Let me grab all the water.
Sick.
That was scary.
I hate that guy.
Please burn alive.
Come on.
Hey, miss.
It's not going to the water or the fire right now.
Get rid of all this oil.
That sludge, that means we can mix.
And I've already been there.
Hey, a broken wand.
Shit.
I want to experiment with that.
Oh, there's also coal pouch.
You know what?
Maybe I will have a pouch on me just to experiment with that stuff.
Let's throw away the worm pheromone.
Don't want it.
I want this.
Coal pouch.
So now I have a pouch and I have a bottle.
Let me grab that wand.
That is now worm pheromone.
What happens if I mix this with certain stuff?
Let me put coal in here.
Oh, wait.
That's water, never mind.
This one.
That just makes a mountain of coal.
That makes sense.
Whiskey.
Does that do anything?
Mix it.
Acceleration.
God damn it.
I feel like the only thing that sort of works here is toxic sludge and water.
That is the only real reaction I've seen in this game.
Of these, I want to throw away the whiskey, I think.
Damn.
Oh, shit.
I just poisoned myself.
I'm actually dangerously close to death here.
Maybe it's time to peace out.
Yeah, I don't even have any more bombs, so I can't really be doing any digging either.
Uh, this... no, wait.
How do I get down easily?
Here.
That's the way.
Here, down.
There we go.
Let's go.
I mean, we can always go back, right?
That's the thing.
In this game, I can just sort of dig up again if I want.
Give me health, yeah.
Okay, let's see here.
That's a lot of damage.
And we have... oh!
Black hole!
And... oh!
Digging.
And I guess this is technically also digging, but a lot of these are shuffle ones.
Ooh, that looks scary.
That's a scary bastard right there.
Is that the same as this, or is it different?
No, that's the big one, right?
Uh, I think I want this one.
Yes.
Give me that instead of... I guess that one.
Let me see.
What?
Oh, no!
The mana mag sucks!
Why didn't I check that?
This is shuffle, but I want the black hole.
I also want this one.
I'm gonna take... hold on.
This is non-shuffle.
Mana mag... oh, but mana charge speed is 10.
This one sucks too.
Gotta be careful there.
This one for sure.
Uh, replace it with... not bad.
Doubles and shit.
Let's take all of this up here.
Let's do a little, uh...
like that.
Man, if only... oh!
Perks!
Let's check perks.
I need to do this first, actually.
Critical hit plus.
Uh, varmit near you evolves into helpful rat minions.
Angry ghost.
No.
I mean, this one could be nice, I guess.
But I kind of just want to re-roll.
But if I re-roll, then I... well, I can always hit the thing.
I can always come back and buy this later if I want to.
But I guess I can also do that with the wand re-roll.
Actually, this wand is not bad.
That's a decent wand right there.
Here's what I'm gonna do.
Let's take these.
Oh, this is also two spells per calf.
Didn't even notice that.
Throw this shit away.
Use this instead.
And put this in here.
Let's see how that works.
Cool.
I mean, it's not super fast.
Also, oh, these add castelay.
So wait a minute.
If I do that...
Oh, that's the same.
Maybe it's only adding castelay between...
Actually, I'm not quite sure.
If I do that, then this should fire... this should be the recharge time that does this, right?
Man is actually okay with this.
It's not the worst.
Let's see this one.
This is 0.02.
If I put this up here instead.
Definitely shoots faster.
The only thing is it's shuffle, but it doesn't matter if I'm just using these, right?
So 0.03, 0.42.
So here's the thing that's confusing.
If this adds a castelay of 0.75, that is the castelay I'm seeing here, right?
That is like three quarters of a second, I would say.
Approximately, right?
So if I remove this, then the recharge time is the one that... this should be slower, basically.
Definitely.
Yeah, okay.
And it makes sense too.
So the thing that confuses me is that castelay is being added with each of these, right?
But maybe that castelay being added is only counting from this one to the next spell in the sequence, you know?
For some reason, I thought these modifiers in the bottom there would affect the stats of the wand itself, if you know what I mean.
So yeah, that's basically what I'm thinking.
I can do this.
This is a decent wand.
But then, maybe this one is better.
Yeah, not bad.
And then there's this one.
That can probably be...
Oh, I could also... hold on.
No, no, because it's shuffled, this is not going to be what I expect then.
But if I do this, it's going to cast both of these at once.
Oh wait, I don't have enough for that.
The mana is not enough.
There we go.
Interestingly that it shoots... oh, the spread is being increased.
Okay.
Yeah.
Only I had an odd mana here.
Or add mana.
I think I like this one the most.
This is like a solid wand.
That's just pure damage right there.
I love it.
Look at the damage.
25.
That's not bad at all.
That's really good.
Let's see what else we had.
We also have this one.
But... and that has digging on it actually.
This is the luminous drill.
But that one is so confusing to me because it seems shit.
I want the big luminous drill.
I had one that was much better, if you remember.
I was able to just through anything and it was crazy.
So yeah.
What should my next one be?
Probably just... just black holes.
And we can put it on the shuffle because it doesn't matter in which order these are fired.
That seems good.
And it shoots one at a time.
So here's the question real quick.
If I do this... see why is that... why does that keep going?
The last wand I had didn't do that.
It was... it sort of stopped right in front of me.
I wonder if that was because I had the projectile field around me and that's what was doing it.
That's the only explanation I have.
And we have rocks and double and disc projectile.
I am thinking of rerolling these because I don't like these.
I have 200... no I have 248 gold.
Let's do it.
Unlimited spells baby!
Extra... oh god damn that's a hard choice!
I think it's gotta be this one though.
Dude, I feel like it's gotta be unlimited spells even though this one is insane.
I don't know if I pick this one, if these will stay here then.
Or if I will get an extra over here you know.
God damn.
I don't trust this right now.
I'm gonna go with unlimited spells.
That one is sick.
So that means... black hole?
Is that unlimited?
Unlimited?
Wait it's not?
Oh no this is not unlimited.
But the stone is like the rock.
I guess that's unlimited.
I mean not bad but I can have unlimited TNT and stuff right?
Let me quickly do this.
Oh wait I can just test like this.
Yeah look at that.
Amazing.
Okay.
Sick stuff.
And now I have no more money but I can always come back so.
This was a heavy spread I think that is.
These are shuffle.
This is non-shuffle.
But the mana charge speed on this one sucks so this is a bad wand.
I don't like that at all.
Okay unfortunately the black hole is not unlimited.
That was honestly the thing that I was hoping for when I took that.
Dang it.
Um so I'm gonna put this at the end.
No let's put this.
Also hold on.
I do have a spell refresh.
So let me just try this real quick again.
Wait did that work or not?
I'm not sure.
Hold on.
Also how far does it go?
It does not work.
No.
Unfortunately it's not unlimited because the number is up here.
If you see the number up here it means it doesn't work.
But I could do this.
I could have a bunch of rocks.
I could shoot rocks at people.
I wonder how much damage that does.
Speed 60.
Uh what if I do double on that?
Oink!
That's two rocks right there.
I mean it's not that fast.
Oh but dude we can put light on it and go back and explore.
Light on the rocks.
Uh then we can also do...
I do kind of like this.
Dynamite we gotta have right?
Gotta have the dynamite.
We could even do this.
No no we cannot do that actually.
That was a joke.
We cannot do that.
We can put a light there.
Here's the question.
Why do I want to shoot two rocks?
Maybe I don't.
Maybe just one is enough.
Let's see how fast it shoots.
Uh I mean...
Yeah that just throws rocks.
That's pretty cool.
I think it's time to go.
Oh uh here's the thing though.
Maybe you don't want to take this yet.
I'm gonna save that.
Oh but wait a minute.
Oh wait wait wait wait.
If I make a hole here now, the gods will be angry because I'm circumventing the the idea that they have put in here right?
So and I don't have that perk.
Oh shit I don't know what to do then.
Maybe I don't want to do this.
I was gonna make a hole through here with my black hole.
Oh wait wait wait hold on what am I gonna do here?
Uh I don't know.
No I'm just gonna go through I think.
It is what it is.
If I find that perk then I'm gonna start doing that stuff.
Okay so now I can I can dig forever because I have unlimited digging with this.
That's actually incredible.
Yo that's a great spell.
I think I tried this once some time ago but I uh forgot how good it is.
Not bad.
And now you know what let's try the rock.
Hold on.
Hehe infinite TNT baby.
Isn't that lovely?
Let's see what we have.
Bunch of chainsaws with heavy spread.
Ooh manamax is low though.
I think I want it.
But which one should I replace?
Maybe this is crazy but I kind of want to replace the black holes.
They're not infinite.
I thought they would be infinite.
But I like having this to increase the speed of spells.
That was a crucial element.
Or I could replace the rock.
Hold on.
This all depends.
This all depends on how powerful that rock is.
Uh I'm gonna I'm gonna go test the rock.
Oh but you know what?
I have an extra rock uh in my thingy up here.
So yeah just fucking replace the rock.
There you go.
I'm sorry Dwayne.
Not today.
Let's see how this works.
Oh spells per cast four.
Huh.
I wonder if this does insane damage if I actually go melee and mess up some fools.
Oh come here.
Wow you have HP.
This is decent damage.
Boom.
There's a party going on over there.
I like that it's sort of homing on them.
Oh that's a lot of lava.
Blow that shit up.
I have to remember I can just dig everywhere with unlimited spells.
There's gold in the floor as well.
Grab it all.
Oh my god.
We're gonna be rich.
Oh hello.
I'm on fire.
Uh right these guys.
What the hell?
Wait that that toxic sludge is electrocuted.
Oh let's uh maybe I'll get rid of the acceleration.
Whoops.
I want this.
Thank you.
This small rock makes you feel very charged.
I want to try and bring this to certain places and see what happens.
Hey that's the man.
That was quick.
That's the portal right there.
Hey.
Dig.
I'm gonna be rerolling perks so much now.
Oh shit.
Actually do have a good amount of HP at this stage of the game.
Like for example you see this?
Look at this wall here.
I want to just try and just fucking go.
Just fucking go.
See what happens.
When will the game say no?
You know what I mean?
But I don't have infinite of this so what I basically need is a spell that can do this but infinitely.
That's what I'm looking for.
Because I'm curious.
I want to test the limits of this game.
Thank you.
These amount of money are ready.
Actually give me some of this.
Thank you.
Oh man there's a bunch of gold up there.
Nice.
Hello.
Be careful.
That could have gone bad.
But I guess I did clear away didn't I?
I didn't yet.
I did now.
Hello.
Oh that's gold in them heals.
600 gold already.
What is that?
Why was that red?
What's that?
What's it say?
Plastic?
Look it says plastic.
What the hell?
How's that plastic?
I've never seen that.
That's weird.
Let's go up here.
God I love having infinite bombs.
This guy also has infinite bombs but I don't love that.
It's only lovable when I have it.
That's when I love it.
Nah I don't know what I'm doing.
Blow it up.
Oh and fire.
Didn't even pay attention.
I was looking over here didn't even see that I was on fire.
Classic.
Some gold on there as well.
Sweet.
Very good.
It's so freeing to go anywhere I want.
Okay this is the entrance.
So toxic sludge.
I can do that.
Mix it up into water.
Maybe I can chainsaw mix.
Chainsaw mix?
Okay.
Bomb mix.
There we go.
That's much safer now.
Hazard has been cleared.
Oops.
I was poisoned.
I love that this thing homes towards them.
It makes it brainless.
That's what I enjoy.
Another wand!
Dude watch.
Let me just get in.
Doesn't even matter.
Yes!
And we get gold in the process.
A teleport!
Fuck yeah.
Short range homing.
And protect our lives towards targets when near them.
Oh that sounds really nice.
And a triple as well.
Oh man.
I think I will replace the black hole.
Black hole is not infinite means I'm not happy.
Fuck yeah man.
Now we have a teleport.
We have dynamite and this one for building wands later.
That go really fast.
Very nice.
Another wand!
I guess we blow everything up.
Oh wait.
I thought that was my bomb.
My bomb is on three now I have to remember.
Bomb three teleport two.
I probably will forget that I have the teleport for a while.
That's usually what happens.
That works.
Okay let me also see this wand here by the way.
It's a no 0.53.
That's not a great wand is it?
This is shuffle that sucks.
I don't like any of this honestly.
But I will blow it up.
That's not the blow up button.
That's the blow up button.
That's the go boom button.
Ah!
Who would have thunk they're making explosions happen all the time.
Set you on fire occasionally.
I think that's the only damage I've taken by the way in this level is me hitting myself.
Whoa!
You like bombs?
Actually a fantastic wand that I have here.
Great start I want.
Oh come on.
All right that's fine.
Thousand gold.
Now I actually forgot so if I reroll perks in one holy mountain I wonder if the prize is also increased in the next.
I don't remember if that was the case or not.
I gotta pay attention.
Let's try and remember that.
Fungus.
These explode.
I think.
Yes.
Kind of want to go in here yeah.
Fungal caverns.
Let's fuck this place up.
The airfield is extremely humid.
Oh.
But that's okay.
I think.
Oh.
Hello froggy.
Uh.
That's actually a decent one I would say right.
Oh it only has two slots.
That's not good.
Never mind.
They got blown up.
In fact this is maybe how I will deal with everyone.
Just blow them the fuck up.
I have infinite.
It's a decent amount of damage.
Oh my god it's amazing.
And also this homing wand that I have here is actually great against these little fuckers.
Because they're hard to hit.
Another wand.
Oh.
We've got frogs.
A big frog.
Uh.
Let's blow them up.
Ghostbuster.
There we go.
That works.
Uh.
Burn the stuff.
There we go.
Off you go.
Flammable gas.
Fuck out of here.
That guy's still alive.
Sparkable with trigger.
A lot of them.
Oh look at this one.
0.07 no shuffle.
Bunch of slots.
340 mana and 100 recharge.
Dude.
That's sick.
I think I want that?
Hold on.
How good is this?
Oh right.
It's a bit weird because they're all like with trigger.
I kind of want to bring it.
Oh man.
Maybe I want to replace this.
Maybe I say fuck this chainsaw stuff.
Or I could...
No.
I like the chain bolt though.
Maybe I replace the dynamite.
Is that a crime?
You know what?
I will leave this wand here for now.
In fact, I'm gonna write down in my notes.
I'm gonna write fungal caverns.
What?
Jesus!
How dare you?
I was typing or writing, I mean.
Maybe I should just pause.
Fungal caverns.
Sick wand.
Go back.
I shall not forget that ever now that I have written it down.
Polymore?
I don't want that.
What's that?
Freezing liquid potion?
What if I drink it?
Oops!
Okay, of course.
That's what happens when that breaks.
No surprise there.
Oh, there's a guy.
Oh!
He shot me!
Wait, is this going through the wall?
What's happening there?
Is that going through walls?
Heart!
A mage!
Nice.
Sweet.
I'm so oily.
Stop being oily.
Got another wand.
Rats.
Energy orb.
Wait, mine is .08?
What the fuck does that mean?
I don't understand.
Oh, spells per cast is two.
So weird.
Let's blow that up.
What the hell is going on up here?
Someone is shooting with a wand, I think.
Oh, I'm scared of wands.
Get him out of my sight.
Oh!
Wait, where am I?
Oh, I'm here.
Uh, I can't see shit, captain.
Let's just hide out here for a moment.
I'm too scared.
Wait, does this work with the light?
It doesn't.
Those enemies!
I killed it.
Thank God.
Don't you fucking hit me with that.
Okay, from now on, mages, number one enemy.
I do not like that they have this capability.
I got him.
And he dropped my... Oh, that's the wand he was shooting.
Oh.
Oh, wait, there's another guy then.
Right?
No, maybe not.
So he also shot those blindness bolts.
Whatever you want to call them.
Can I make my way through here?
Can I?
Not quite.
But I can just do this.
Uh,
what's happening there?
Oh, my God.
Mix.
It's funny how you can physically mix because everything is simulated.
Okay.
Goodbye.
Oh, shit.
A pair just came out of nowhere.
So that's the bottom.
That was the perfect hit.
Wand.
All right, I can't get through steel.
How am I gonna do this?
Let's go like that.
What the fuck just happened there?
The thing glitched up there.
Look!
That was a crazy discovery just now.
What the hell?
I did it twice in a row.
Acceleration.
But I can get up there, though.
Sort of.
Nice.
Any enemies?
There's an enemy.
Hey, that's for you.
You like this?
Oh, no.
Dude, this thing totally shoots through steel.
Look.
I honestly don't know if that's intended.
Where did that wand go?
Oh.
Spitterbolt with timer.
Terrible mana charge speed.
Don't want it.
What is this space age music?
What's happening here?
Why does it feel like I'm tripping?
Whoa!
Oh, shit.
Just keep shooting.
Keep shooting.
Good thing we have homing, huh?
Kill him.
Come on.
Oh, thank God.
That could have been really bad.
What's up, guys?
Having fun?
Anything else?
Thank you.
Mix it up.
Oh, another Ukuskivi.
Let's see what we got here.
A magic missile.
And the wand is shit.
All right.
I'm starting to pay more attention to the stats of the wand.
That's not something I did a lot earlier, but I'm really doing it because I just want a great wand.
There's only one thing guys want, and it's fucking disgusting.
Get him.
Look at all this blood.
All these wands!
Look at it!
Uh, ooh.
Giga disc projectile, spark bolt, luminous drill, all kinds of things.
0.12 seconds.
That's not bad, I guess.
I mean, not bad.
What's this?
Whiskey potion and slimy egg?
Hold on now.
Say what?
Oh, no.
I done fucked up, didn't I?
I done goofed.
This is a goof.
I goofed.
The goofening.
I didn't think about that.
I'm scared of touching that now.
Yeah, I did.
Nope, nope.
How am I gonna get through that?
Probably just destroy this over here.
Beautiful.
What do we have?
Speed up!
Hello, I like that a lot.
Oh, but I don't have enough... should I just get rid of my bombs?
That's a...
I can probably find more later, right?
I can probably find more later.
Oh, dude.
Shit.
I don't know.
Maybe I'll do it.
I'll take it.
I like speed up a lot.
But if I need to dig now, I have a problem, right?
So maybe I will just not do it anyway and come back for this want later.
Let me note that down.
Deep in fungal caverns.
Speed up.
Cool.
Honestly, I'm probably never gonna get back here, but on the off chance, you know, that's gonna be waiting for me.
Let's see what else we have.
A wand again.
Shit.
Wow, they sort of loop between enemies.
Very cool.
Release the acid or toxic sludge.
That is a shit wand.
Actually, it's not.
Actually, it is.
Yep.
It ain't good, bro.
Look at this.
Water.
Mix.
Stir shit up.
Hand over the money.
Look how much money I have, by the way.
Ball lightning.
Interesting.
Burning... Oh, dude.
210 mana max points.
But it shoots two spells per cast.
Two spells per cast, right?
Oh, man.
I want that.
Let's try it.
Wait a minute.
Oh, I'm not in the fun... I just realized I'm not even in the fungal caverns anymore.
I gotta go back this way.
Okay.
Let me try this here.
Ooh.
Six damage and explode.
Oh.
I mean, pretty cool, I guess.
And that is a projectile.
70 mana drain.
Oof.
That's a lot.
Gotta experiment, though.
Now I still don't have digging, though.
That's the thing.
Maybe it's time to go through the portal.
Is it, though?
I feel like I'm not done here.
Ah, you know what?
I can always come back.
This is just a start, right?
We don't know what's in store for us.
We can find the craziest perks.
Basically, what I'm afraid of is... Oh, man.
I would love to not anger the gods, you know what I mean?
But still sort of be able to change my wants.
That is, like, the thing.
Oh, wait.
Let's go.
We have 2,000 gold.
Should be able to make something do with this.
Don't heal yet.
Oh, nice.
We get to two spells.
Damage.
I love the damage.
What's this?
Cursed sphere.
And, ooh, teleport, Matt.
I already have that.
Digging bolt.
Was that the one that was super good?
What's this?
Circle of acid.
Yeah, no, thanks.
Let's see the perks.
Personal plasma beam.
You constantly fire a devastating plasma beam, but you fire spells much slower.
What?
Okay, look.
Recharge cost is 400 now.
So it does sort of go from mountain to mountain.
That's confirmed now.
Critical hit plus.
No, faster projectiles.
Your projectile spells fly faster than before.
That seems really good.
Dude, that's like having the... Oh, I don't have it on me now, but you know, the spell, the projectile modifier, but having it on all the time.
You know?
Oh, kind of want to re-roll though.
Oh, dude, I don't know.
Should I re-roll?
I'm conflicted.
Hold on.
Before I take this, let me see if I make a one that will utilize the faster projectiles anyway.
That's like the thing.
I definitely want damage plus.
I'm going to take this.
I want to try.
What do I want to try?
Maybe...
Hold on.
I also have other things, no?
Short range homing.
I have that stuff.
I also have these.
What's that?
Firebomb?
Circle of acid.
So here's the thing.
Cursed sphere.
I wonder if that's something that is usually
limited in casts, but now I can shoot it infinitely, you know?
Maybe.
Let's see what this does.
Oh, that is cursed.
That's super weird.
But if I take this, it's going to go faster, right?
15 damage.
That's nothing to scoff at.
What if I do...
Let's see here.
Triple spell.
One, two, three.
And I add 10 damage to them all.
So no, that way I have to do it like this, right?
Let's see how much damage that does.
In fact, I should be testing things over here.
Oh, the thing is, this is an electric wand.
That's dangerous.
Like a hundred something damage.
Not bad.
Oh, you know what I want to try?
Uh, first off, let's try this.
Uh, wait.
Is it because the wand is so bad?
What's going on here?
Recharge.
Super long on this.
What if I put it on here?
Ah, that looks better.
Why is there no sound?
Is that a bug?
There's no sound at all when I do this.
A bolt that is ideal for mining operations.
What the hell?
Oh, there's a little bit of a sound there now.
Hold on.
Is there anything I can dig here?
It's all like very solid material.
I can't really get through it, unfortunately, but that looks good to me.
Why not do this?
I mean, it's shuffle, but I don't know if that does any difference at all, but that is definitely something that goes fast, right?
I don't know if that is actually digging through things though.
Here's the thing.
I would like something that would ideally dig through this piece.
That wouldn't be bad.
Let's see here.
This one casts four spells per cast.
That's actually quite something.
So what I could do here, but was this one terrible?
It has a long recharge time, right?
Oh wait, man is also an issue?
Yeah, it is.
Okay.
Now the short-range homing.
Let's see how that works.
Probably put it on this one then.
Just for testing.
Does this hurt me?
Oh man, I'm scared.
A projectile that brings bad luck to anyone it hits.
What the hell does that mean?
I am too curious about that, dude.
Dude, short-range homing rock.
Is it homing towards anything?
Oh, wow.
Okay.
Wait, is that an enemy up there?
No, wait, that's just the thing.
Look at that.
It's like magnetic.
I remove rocks.
Yo, the damage I do with this is actually nuts.
What the hell?
But I guess it's melee, so.
All right.
Rocks have... rocks are gone.
But my screen is still shaking.
That's weird.
I don't know what to make.
I think I'm gonna try this out.
This is... this seems cool.
You know, that seems cool.
Maybe we don't need all of these.
Like that, that's definitely gonna dig, I think, to do most things.
And then we can have a... we need a... we need a damage wand.
Just something purely damaged, right?
And I think the best way to do this is to do the chain bolts and use the damage plus on them.
Wherever that is.
Here.
So I'm not sure I like the ball lightning very much.
Also, I'm afraid of lightning.
That shit scares me.
So instead, let's just put this in here.
Three of them at once.
See, that's pretty sweet.
But the issue is, the reason it takes so long between shots is because the recharge of the mana is actually not enough.
So what if I just use a double instead?
You don't need that much anyway.
No, wait, that is okay.
Oh, wait a minute.
Why does that take so long?
This adds cast delay, right?
Bro, I'm so confused.
That's so slow.
This one sucks.
Ah, dude, I don't know.
I don't know what to do.
This one.
Is that the one I had before?
What is the one I had before actually?
Was it just this one?
Or was it probably that one, right?
Yeah, I think so.
But it's shuffle.
So, you know, it's not the greatest thing in the world.
It works.
Now, damage wand.
I could go for something like...
Let's say extra damage on spheres.
Oh, wait, I also have stuff over here.
I have to remember.
I have the spark bolt.
Let me see how fast this is.
So here's the thing.
If I now add stuff like this...
Is that faster?
It's such a weird system.
Hmm, three.
No, yeah, yeah.
Dude, this.
No, that.
That.
Oh, but what I need is something with trigger, right?
That is like the whole thing.
I don't want to do what I'm trying to do here.
Unless...
How much damage is this even?
I don't think it's enough for me to be happy.
Maybe I do want to use this.
I mean, it's a decent amount of damage, right?
That shit got destroyed.
I mean, that is a good amount of damage.
It's not bad.
In fact, I like it.
Three of them, bam.
Recharge is decent, you know.
Castelae, castelae.
So the castelae is definitely the bottleneck there.
And that wand is really crap, because it only has 56 mana.
So that can maybe be my teleport.
You know?
Put this up here.
Yeah.
Oh, it's actually really slow.
It's that bad, even for teleport.
Oh, shit.
God damn it.
So let's do this.
That's terrible now.
How did I do this before with the wand?
Was it this one or that one?
I think I used this one.
Dude, I have shit combinations!
I can't seem to find a good wand to make.
I can't.
Unless I... unless the rock is actually... I wish I could see the damage on the rock, you know?
Because if that actually homes towards enemies and that does a shit ton of damage, that would be sick.
Although then I have the flying rock to worry about.
That shit scares the crap out of me, similar to the propane tanks.
Flying everywhere, you know?
If they hit me, I'm fucked.
I wish I had more slots up here to store my spells, man.
I don't have enough.
It's not enough for me.
Is that gonna be my teleport wand?
It's still kind of slow.
The recharge on it is terrible.
That one is also bad.
All of this is bad.
Maybe I'll have to disregard this.
Maybe I don't want to do this anymore with this.
You know?
Get rid of it.
Better.
That's definitely a teleport wand right there.
We're using that.
Done.
That's the teleport wand.
Next.
This may be my damage wand.
I mean, it's very short range.
It's not terribly amazing.
But you know, it's a lot better than what I had.
So there's that.
Let me try this actually.
So this shoots two spells per cast, which means this one and another one.
Which could be...
What if I... So that should technically shoot this one and that one.
How does that work?
Long cast delay on that.
I want to try the homing rock for sure.
And then I'm gonna take this.
Faster projectiles.
Although the homing does seem to speed it up, right?
So maybe in that case... Oh, you know what?
I can also re-roll.
I think I'm gonna re-roll.
I don't like these perks right here that much.
Let's see.
Close call.
You gain additional chance to deal critical hits as long as there are enemies near you.
Homing shots.
God damn it.
Repelling cape.
Stains drop at a fast rate when moving.
God damn it.
Okay, I don't like these that much either.
I mean homing shots.
Sure.
Why not?
What's this?
All right.
I'm taking homing shots.
It's gonna... Okay, we're gonna go all in on the homing.
We're homing so hard.
So we're gonna short-range homing and the homing perk.
Let's see how this works.
It's wanting to go somewhere up there.
That's a lot of homing, baby.
Let's try that.
I mean, fuck it.
Worst case, we die, right?
And that's it.
This one...
is terrible because it has a long recharge.
So how can we remedy that?
Can we remedy that at all?
It's also shooting four spells at the same time.
Maybe I'll disregard this wand.
I think I used this wand to do this before, didn't I?
Yeah.
You know what?
I think I'm gonna go with this.
Look at that.
That seems crazy, right?
And then we're just gonna have a shitty teleport.
That's fine.
Shitty teleport it is.
We're doing it, baby.
Also, that rock is starting to piss me off over there.
Let's also... Can they hurt me?
I'm so scared.
This is a test for science.
I don't think they should be hurting me, right?
If they were hurting me.
Get rid of these damn rocks.
Stop making sound.
The statue, it's all fucked.
Oh my god.
Oh, you know what?
I'm also gonna do this.
That's a modifier.
Let's put this on top as well.
Let's just add some damage to that.
Now the last wand here, that sucks.
What can I do on that?
Maybe I'll just play with this.
You know?
Experiment a little bit with that thing.
And that costs 40 mana.
This has 56 mana max, but it does recharge quick.
So let's see.
But that's not really the issue.
The issue is actually the recharge time.
So... and it shoots four spells at the same time.
I could just throw a bunch of bullshit in here.
Burning trail.
And heavy spread.
Heavy spread does what?
Actually reduces recharge time a little bit.
And how about some energy spheres?
Oh shit!
Okay, but at least that... I know it doesn't damage me now.
That's a test confirmed there.
A heavy spread bad.
We don't want that.
Get rid of this.
Why does these not... Oh, it probably doesn't have enough mana for that.
Yeah, that's probably what's happening.
Mmm.
It sucks.
It's a really shitty wand.
It is what it is though.
I think I'm ready to move on.
Oh dude, I have an idea by the way.
I wait to game the system a little bit here.
Uh, let's see here.
We also have this stuff.
What was this?
Freeze charge.
Remind me.
Gives the projectile a frozen charge that it will release an impact.
Sure.
Fire and frozen.
What does that do?
I mean, cool.
Let's do that.
And then we also have... uh, you know, spark bolt is actually not bad.
In fact, hold on.
Ooh, wait a minute.
Could I make a really sick wand here?
This only costs five mana to shoot.
But long recharge time.
Nah, leave this up here for now.
Teleport.
We have the rock.
In fact, maybe I should put the damage plus down here because this one doesn't have a... this is like... okay, so here's the thing.
I think this is like similar to when I kick things in the world and they hit enemies and they do damage.
I think that's based on momentum.
Because this doesn't have a damage modifier on it, so I think... I think using this is a waste on it.
I think I should put this here, if anything, to make this do a little more damage.
This is just a test anyway to see how that works.
Anyway, check this out.
What if I do this?
So I know everything collapses right here, right?
What if I cheat the system?
Can I go through like this?
No, okay.
Well, basically what I was thinking is if there's like a spot where the game registers you leaving, maybe if I teleport it won't register that spot, you know?
Whoa, that guy just died!
How much damage was that?
What?
How... how much damage was that?
Excuse me?
Oh wait, I didn't heal.
Oh my god, hold on.
I forgot to heal.
Holy shit.
Hopefully I can get back up.
Oh wait, I can do this, of course.
Uh, let's see how good this is now.
The real test.
Oh, it's actually... it's pretty good!
Hey, I made a sick thinking wand!
Yay!
Awesome!
Yeah, uh, let's use...
This one is useless, I guess?
Spell refresher?
No, it's actually not useless.
Because black holes, for example.
But I can't get through this material, unfortunately.
Also, look at the board up there.
It's like... yeah.
It's shooting off digging bolts and chainsaws randomly, right?
One at a time and it's random, because it's shuffle.
But it does it so fast, because all these chainsaws reduce recharge time.
But what about the... oh, I guess the castelay is very low to begin with.
.03, so this has no effect.
Yeah.
So basically how that is working, is that this is the one that's digging.
The other ones do not do anything.
The effect is there.
You see the gold?
You know, it's there, but it's not actually digging at all.
This is just making it so this one fires more often.
Which is what's actually doing the digging here.
Yep.
What's that?
Brass!
So wait, let me see this rock.
What is the damage?
I didn't see the damage.
Show me the damage.
22.
600?
Oh, it's definitely based on speed.
Oh, I should have taken the speed up perk.
Wait, what was that?
Dude, I can just do this.
Find a target.
Oh, shit, that takes damage from that.
Be careful here.
It just killed a bunch of enemies.
This is broken as fuck.
What the fuck?
4,000!
That did 4,000 damage.
Dude.
800.
This is insanity.
This is broken.
Damn.
Look at this thing.
Critical plus.
Sweet.
But I like this.
Do I like that actually?
Hold on.
It doesn't even shoot.
I don't even have enough mana for this.
I fucked that one up bad.
Goddamn.
That is probably the biggest fail wand I've ever made.
Kivaskivi.
Sure.
I'll take it.
Let's release the water.
Oh my god, the digging is nuts.
Uh, no.
Thank you.
We also have a wand here.
Reduce spread.
Bubbly bounce.
I actually really like reduce spread.
Like minus 60 degrees is insane.
Wand is actually... Oh, it's shuffle wand.
I hate that.
Look, only 43 damage because the rock was slow.
So wait, it just goes through an enemy and goes to the next enemy?
There's no way that's what's happening because that's insanity.
Come on, find something.
Come on, boy.
Off you go.
They found a mark.
I think.
I'm still a little worried about that rock being able to hurt me.
I'm not entirely sure that's... Oh, is there an enemy embedded in the ice there?
Hold on.
That totally looks like an enemy in the ice.
No, okay.
Can I dig through the brass?
So I could technically go back up now because I'm in the snowy depths.
But I don't think I want to do that yet.
What's that?
Chili egg?
What?
Hold on.
I found a new friend.
Fuck off.
The egg feels cold.
Okay.
Hamis!
I have a Hamis pet.
Oh my god.
Press E to pet?
The Hamis is happy?
That's awesome.
Actually amazing.
Rock!
That's not an enemy.
Motherfucker.
I'm so sorry.
It wasn't me.
God damn.
Oh, fuck.
I was about to name him and everything.
I think that's my rock.
3,000.
Jesus.
How?
Oh my god.
This is a sick wand.
I may have broken the game.
I think I broke the game here.
This is unprecedented.
Someone's shooting.
Oh, I can't get through that though.
Oh, that's a bummer.
Steel is a no-go.
See, that's why... Oh man, I want something else to dig with.
Also, I have to remember I can do this.
I keep forgetting I have a teleporter.
I feel like I should have a wand just... Oh, Jesus.
God damn.
What the hell is that?
Wait, I can't get in here?
It doesn't dig through this either.
Oh boy, that's definitely a trap.
Yikes.
How do we deal with that?
There's a rock up there.
These rocks are wild.
I just sent it off and it's gonna find something.
Bastards.
I can even kick the rocks into action.
Go.
Come on, go.
Kill him.
That's frick.
Why is he not dead?
Hello.
Get him.
It's a bit janky though, this weapon.
At least he's trapped.
He's not gonna get out of there.
He's having a bad day.
At least the rock doesn't hurt me.
It one shots these guys.
I need something that can break these things.
I need a proper wand actually is what I need.
Why is there a lantern?
Jesus fucking Christ.
Dude, I wonder how this will do against the bosses.
You know?
In fact, the rock blocked the shot.
Hey, calm down up there.
Oh shit, it needs to be closer though.
See,
I should have taken a speed up instead, I think.
Because the homing on this is actually enough.
It's short range homing, I guess.
But yeah, okay.
I'm not actually sure.
I'm not sure.
I'm not sure what would be enough.
Anyway, what I was about to say is I think I'm gonna go up to the boss in the hemisphere and try and fuck him up with this weapon because this seems insane.
I haven't killed a guy yet and I need to kill him.
Steal.
I can make my way through here though.
Burn!
I'll wait.
See, I'm gonna let... I'm gonna gate... open the path here for my rock.
There, go!
Glowing lance!
But do I even like that now that I have a rock?
I don't think I do.
Rock is my new best friend.
Get me out of here.
Oh my god.
Just kill everything.
What is that?
It's oil, okay.
Orbiting arc.
Sparkbolt with trigger.
Hmm, I don't know.
I don't know about that one.
Also, it's shuffle, so.
Ripperino!
Damn.
Oh, one rock is enough.
It will clear an area.
Uh, I don't like that at all.
Snow.
Bye-bye.
Okay.
This is one of my favorite weapons.
Just the rock.
The homing rock.
And you know what else?
I actually had this setup available to me at some point, if you remember.
I tried this in the holy mountain and it went flying everywhere.
But I think I was too afraid to use it because of it hitting me.
Whoops.
I don't want that one either.
Wait, what's this?
Magical temple?
Oh, it doesn't dig through that.
Oh, actually.
Say what now?
Oh, wait, wait.
Is this a dark place?
It is.
I don't have any lights.
Shit.
What I do have is a rock.
Get him!
Oh, wait.
Does this not hit ghosts?
Come on.
Tell me.
Oh, no!
Wait, what?
He's sort of stuck there, though.
I can hurt him.
Oh, okay.
So there are limitations to this.
It's not as OP as I thought.
Oh, yeah.
It's wanting to get in here.
I can make that happen.
Let's try again.
Will that really not kill?
That means I actually need a proper wand.
This wand is like an extra one to have, you know, for special circumstances when the situation calls for it.
Whoops.
Can I kick that?
Yeah, doesn't do anything to them.
I mean, I have this.
It does do a good amount of damage.
Honestly, the digging wand.
Yes!
Kills those guys, at least.
What's that?
It's diamond, right?
What's going on down there?
I don't like that one bit.
Magical temple.
It won't kill this guy, either, it seems.
Oh, wait.
It's on the other side of the wall.
Maybe it will kill him.
Dude, it totally traps them in place, look.
You mad, bruh?
Whoops.
Yeah, I don't have the optimal wands for this.
The ghosts are causing problems for me.
So I think it's time we leave here.
In fact, I'm going to go try and kill that boss.
We got to try new things here.
Let's see if we can kill the boss up there with this.
Because last time when I used traditional spells on him, he didn't take any damage at all.
It's like everything was bouncing off of him.
Maybe this will do the trick, you know?
A good old rock.
These guys trapped.
Have fun, man.
Wait, why did that just drop two gold?
I just noticed.
That's weird.
Unless that was two rats in one, and they just sort of overlaps or something.
I can't get in here!
I need to wand!
Let's go this way.
I don't think I've heard this song before.
Usually there's a different song in here.
Uh, that guy's gonna wake up, no?
Or not.
I've been here already.
Let me start digging.
Hell yeah.
Hello!
Don't you shoot me.
It killed him, look!
I want to kill the sniper.
Where are you?
There you are.
Ain't no match for the mighty rock.
A boulder.
Oh, I checked this one already, I think.
So we gotta go up and to the right.
Good.
Oh, concentrated mana!
You gain mana back faster.
That's actually...
How much faster though?
What are we talking?
Whoa!
That's a lot of concentrated mana.
In fact... Oh, I don't have another potion unfortunately, but I did want to fill it up with it.
Let's remember that.
If I find another potion, I'll come back here and grab some.
Could come in handy.
Dude, I keep forgetting I
have a charm on toxic sludge.
Does this count as toxic sludge, I wonder?
Let me grab this gold.
I think we're approaching the point.
Let me grab more water.
There we go.
This is it.
Oh wait, how am I gonna get up there?
I mean, I can probably just get up there actually.
It's not like I need levitation or anything.
I don't think so, at least.
No, I totally did this without, I think, at one point.
Oh, you know what?
I'm gonna try and put this broken wand on the altar there.
Maybe that will do something.
At some point, I can't keep going on the right.
I have to switch to the other side.
At least that's what happened last time.
Oh, here we go.
Let's go.
Wait, I can't dig in this, right?
Actually, I can.
But then... oh wait.
No, okay, so I can only... oh wait, I'm stuck.
I can only dig in dense rock, I think, but extremely dense.
No, it totally works.
It does work.
It's just...
really... it works, but it also really doesn't work.
It's a bit weird.
Wait, how am I gonna... oh, of course.
So, actually, hold on, is this a bad idea?
I feel like I could always come back with more HP later.
Ooh, am I doing something stupid?
Wait a minute.
I could just go over here, actually.
You know what?
I've changed my mind.
I'm gonna do this later.
Oh wait, I can't cross that, though.
I was gonna go back through the holy mountain there.
And now that I have so much money...
Nah, fuck it, I'm doing it.
I'm doing it.
Oh, wait.
I fucked up.
Oh, come on.
Go this way.
Kind of want to dig my way into that little area in there where there's a secret.
But I can't dig like that.
Okay, here we go.
I have... I believe in my stone.
You gotta believe with me here.
It's happening.
Enter the orb room.
Weird that it's just called an orb room, isn't it?
Let me just see this again.
Okay.
I got it.
I now have two orbs collected.
All right, dude.
Are you ready?
Fuck you.
Tell me that's doing damage to you.
It's not doing shit.
Oh, no.
Ah, wait, he's using a wand?
Look.
Yeah, okay.
I'm out of here.
See you, bitch.
Fucking hell, that guy is just immune to damage, it seems.
Weird.
But, I mean, I got the health, so fuck you.
I'll come back later with something else.
Dude, maybe the nuke is what you need.
Since I found it up there close to him but hidden away, you know.
That could be the secret weapon to defeating that guy.
Maybe that's his only weakness.
Ah, a nuke.
My only weakness.
How'd you know?
I think
a nuke is pretty much everyone's only weakness.
Or weakness, not only, but definitely one of weaknesses.
Let's just continue fucking people up down here.
I have so much goddamn money.
That guy dropped two!
Wait, what is happening?
Why are enemies dropping two gold?
Ambrosia?
That's really good.
Get rid of this shit.
Fuck!
I didn't want that ambrosia anyway.
Can't believe I did that.
Rock for you.
And you.
What's this?
Oh, dude, watch, watch.
A tiny amount?
Mix it with the rock.
Look how the water spreads!
Mix
it up good!
Oops.
Ah, damn.
83 HP.
That's actually a little bit too close, maybe.
4000 damage.
Okay, we're leaving.
Nah, fuck this.
We're out of here.
We gotta use those money, man.
This is... We have too much money.
Before we take the health, let's see the perks.
First things first.
I don't even want to look at the ones.
Let's see, what do we have?
A potato.
Iron stomach.
You no longer suffer from negative effects of eating.
Exploding corpses?
Nah.
Explosion immunity?
That's an oldie but a goodie.
But...
I mean, it's great.
But it's also an oldie.
I kind of want a nudie.
Okay, what's that?
Strong levitation, boo.
Revenge tentacle, boo.
Telekinetic kick.
Yes!
I love that perk!
That's a great perk.
What a weird wand.
Lance.
Okay, let's see the stats now.
Point... it's... I'll fucking shuffle.
Point 0.3.
Dude, mana charge speed on this is sick, though.
Point 0.8.
Spells per cast is 3.
That's a... that's a decent wand, I think.
Spread is zero!
Not bad.
I think I may want that.
Um...
Let's see here.
Let me throw away some stuff that I don't want.
I don't... I don't think I want the energy spheres.
I don't want that one either.
Do I want this one?
Maybe... I already have a teleport so we can get rid of that.
Whoops.
Throw it down there.
The heavy spread.
Don't want it.
Let's put this over here.
Organize it a little bit.
I don't think I want the disc projectile.
I have a rock.
That's all a man needs.
Maybe I don't need all of these, because I don't think I'm going to use these anyway, but they do seem cool as fuck, so I'm going to keep them for a while.
Uh... I do want spark bolts, though, actually.
Hold on.
Take these off.
That one is actually amazing.
Lightning bolt.
Oh, dude.
Lightning bolts.
Oh, boy.
This is not a modifier, never mind.
But this is actually a...
This is the easy one to make, you know?
Just a straight-up lightning bolt.
That's a possibility.
Let's see.
Then we also have...
I don't know what that one is.
Or that one.
But let's take this one.
Electric charge.
That will release on impact.
I feel like that could go wrong really quick.
Let me get rid of some of these.
So I don't want this one.
I do want this one.
So this one, I think, is really good.
0.1 seconds cast delay only.
Decent mana max, decent mana charge.
And zero spread.
And it's non-shuffle, and it has a lot of slots.
Can you ask for more, you know?
So let's make a standard damage wand here.
I mean, we could just do this, of course, but that's a little bit boring.
That works.
That is the...
Oh, shit, I can't figure out how to make a good wand situation that I make with that.
That's the deal.
So if I use chainsaws here, I can actually make some crazy shit.
So how do we want to do this?
I think I just want spark bolts on mass.
So maybe I do a triple spark bolts, but what if they all have trigger?
That's the thing I don't quite...
So this is going to shoot three spells at the same time.
That, that, and that.
Ping!
It shoots off, right?
What happens then?
Let's actually test.
Will that work the same?
Let's say there's a...
What's an easy thing to do?
Let's say there's a cursed sphere at the end.
Right?
We know this one will cast another spell upon collision.
So will this cast three cursed spheres because all three of these collide with a wall?
Wait.
It shoots it once.
Oh, right.
It goes like, bop, bop, bop, because this triggers that which...
But that's the thing.
That's the thing that confuses me here.
Whoops.
I just murdered a fish.
Bop, bop, bop.
So what I'm seeing is happening is that this is being fired.
It triggers that.
Which triggers that.
But why is that happening?
All of these are in a triple spell.
Right?
That's the thing I don't understand here.
This should not be happening the way I see this here.
That's confusing me.
So if I do...
Let's say I didn't have this, right?
What happens then?
Is that the exact same behavior?
It is!
The hell?
I don't get that.
That's weird as hell.
Let me try this now.
Just makes it shoot faster.
Pretty cool.
Neat stuff.
If I now add another one...
Even faster.
Let's see what it does.
It shoots one of these.
And it shoots three of these and that.
So if I now do a...
I also have a normal spark bolt actually.
Spark bolt.
If I shoot that first...
Hold on.
I need to understand how this works completely here now.
Because I made a wand last run.
And it was super good.
And I think I only understood slightly what was happening.
I sort of experimented until something clicked.
And I didn't really understand why it worked.
But it just worked.
So if I now shoot three things.
Let's make it simple.
Let's shoot two things.
This is a double spell.
This will shoot that and that.
What if we do...
Not that.
Hold on.
Change it.
If I now do just that.
That should shoot a spark bolt.
Done.
It hits the recharge time.
No, it hits cast delay.
And then it shoots the next.
This one casts another spell upon collision.
What is it gonna cast?
Well, it's gonna wrap around.
Right?
Because there's nothing here.
Let's see.
Yeah.
So it shoots that first and then it shoots that with that.
You see?
Understood.
Cool.
Let's move on.
We do two now.
Here.
Let's try and predict.
See, in my head, this should do...
That one and that one at the same time.
They both get shot at the same time.
And then when this one impacts...
It shoots off another spell.
And that spell is the double spell.
Right?
What?
Unless this doesn't count as a spell.
Maybe the double spell itself is not considered a spell.
I mean, it's not, right?
It's a multicast, I guess.
So what I really should be saying is it's not a projectile.
That's the big deal.
Wait, where's my damage modifier thing?
Did I have that?
Was it this one?
Oh yeah, I want this real quick.
Hold on.
Uh, give me this stuff.
I want that.
And I want these.
Just put them here for now.
And then throw away this wand, because nobody likes it.
There we go.
So I want to damage up on this, for sure.
Let's go...
Hold on.
There's actually one over here as well.
There's one on each side.
Okay.
So if I now do that...
It just shoots faster.
And the reason is...
What is the reason?
Let's think.
The reason is, this one reduces the recharge time.
Right?
Honestly, there's something about this chainsaw that I don't understand.
It says, also has some magical properties.
What does that mean?
You know?
Oh wait, speed 200.
Is that the magical property?
Speed 800.
Probably not.
No, that's just an inherent stat on it.
Uh, if I now, let's just naively put a bunch.
Just see what happens.
Maybe we can explain it.
Actually, I'm gonna look at the board.
It does that first.
And then it shoots that.
Okay, it never reaches these, it seems.
Maybe there's not enough mana.
So this makes sense.
So definitely want to put this here.
So the double damage or the damage affects all of it, right?
Oh, that shoots really fast now.
Why?
Okay, why?
Let's see.
When I click...
Oh, it's really hard to see.
So, it definitely shoots all the way to here.
And then it shoots that one.
Actually, that makes sense.
Because it shoots the double, right?
Which contains two spells.
That one.
And, well, that one.
Why is this in it then?
What does this do?
Hold on, let me remove this.
Interesting.
But if I add this, it alternates.
See, that makes sense.
That makes sense.
But if I do this, it's a very different behavior.
Yeah, okay, so here it doesn't bounce off.
So the trigger doesn't work here.
Aha.
What if I were to do this?
You see the trigger is going, bam, bam, bam, bam, bam, bam.
It sort of bounces off, right?
Because it triggers a spell where it collides.
So, let's see here.
I'm basically trying to understand the one I made last time.
Because this is quite similar to the stuff I had last time, right?
If I put a triple here...
What happens then?
It shoots that one, that one, and that one.
These are all projectiles.
So that's... that makes sense.
Fine, I'll remove this.
And it does that.
Okay.
What if I put a chainsaw here?
Because I think I had something like that as well last time.
What?!
How does that make any sense?
Holy fucking shit, that's fast.
Issue though, we don't have mana.
That's why I had add mana last time.
Let's try another... why does this...
Why... hold on, how much damage is this?
That's a lot of damage, damn it, damn it!
Holy shit!
So it shoots double damage or like damage on the chainsaw.
And then it goes triple...
that.
Wait, what?
Triple chain damage chain?
Triple... wait, what?
Triple... that.
So it shoots... I don't get it.
I do not understand.
Oh!
Is that even faster?
Hold on, it's actually not.
Oh, let me recharge mana, let's see here.
220.
I watch, if I remove this...
It's way more.
What?!
I'm doing something crazy here and I'm not understanding what's happening.
You know?
What if I do that?
Like the same.
I mean, this is a solid standard damage wand, you know?
It's not bad.
It requires some extra mana, of course.
It's not really too feasible right now.
But it's enough for one enemy, you know?
If you just want to brrrr!
Or destroy some environmental shit.
But then our digging...
Oh, wait, what if I put the digging in here?
Dude, wait!
Can I start digging at a distance?
Wait a minute, I need a rock.
Dude!
That is phenomenal!
Oh yeah!
Oh wait, now it's not...
Wait a minute, I need to see the board.
Hold on.
Okay.
Wow, man.
The chainsaw is a fucking mystery to me.
I've...
It says it also has some magical properties.
I have no earthly clue what the fuck that means.
You know?
I understand that it reduces recharge time.
But why does it shoot so fast suddenly?
Because look at this.
The cast delay is 0.1, right?
This only affects the recharge time.
It reduces 0.17 seconds from that.
It's 0.5 right now.
This adds cast delay.
So we're now at 0.18.
This adds even more cast delay.
And some crit, it seems, actually.
I never noticed that.
Uh...
This adds more cast delay.
Actually reduces recharge time as well.
So...
Recharge time is now minus...
I don't even know, like 34.
So like, that would be...
16.16 is it now?
And then...
Actually, oh!
So recharge time is actually almost zero.
But the cast delay is 0.1.
Maybe that is what is explaining this.
I mean, 0.1 is not that much.
It's quite fast.
So maybe this is just the effect of removing all the recharge time.
Really, that's like the thing.
Let me see here.
So it's digging now.
But look, it's not doing as much damage when I do it like this.
If I put this here...
Damage is twice, actually.
But the digging is no longer happening.
Watch.
At least it's very reduced.
You see that?
So if I now do this instead...
What then?
Digging is still sort of terrible.
What if I put this...
In front?
Mm-hmm.
Oh!
Uh...
Excuse me, sir.
You're drunk.
Go home.
The hell just happened there?
My dude is having a...
Some issues.
I mean, 265, 264.
Now the issue... Here's the thing.
Can I make a digging one somewhere else?
Let's say I do this.
And I add...
That at the end.
Let's see.
Oh, probably put it on the non-shuffle.
Or, yeah, for now.
But...
Stay there!
So if I now do this...
That will dig, but...
It's terrible.
It is terrible.
It's weird.
Yeah, I don't think I get it.
Let's instead of this...
Just do that.
Whoa!
Wait.
Wait a minute.
Excuse me?
That is...
Wait.
That is totally shooting off multiple.
Super fast.
But see, that makes no sense.
Because look what it says.
0.83 castalace being added.
The recharge time is nowhere near zero now.
How does that work?
Look, my mana is instantly gone.
Because it's casting it so rapidly.
Hey!
That's actually sick!
I mean, it's not a fantastic amount of damage here, but...
Oh, I guess I need to add this, I guess.
But yeah.
Let's see here.
Not bad, I guess.
But see, why is this one so much better?
I guess because it releases...
Oh, wait, what?
What?
0.05?
Oh, wait, these are not...
Maybe it just increases the speed because it casts another spell upon...
Oh, wait, no, wait, I understand what's happening, I think.
It shoots that.
In fact, it shoots two of these.
Oh, triple.
One, two, three.
And then it shoots a single.
And the single is the first one.
So that's just like there.
It's just being shot.
It's off.
This is actually a sick wand.
I'm going to leave it like this.
I'm going to leave it like that.
That's fine.
This one here.
How about we...
We can probably still make a digging wand out of this.
I still have some chainsaw.
Like this should be fine, right?
Probably not amazing, but...
Was it like that I had it?
That can still dig, I think.
Let's see.
Yay!
We can still dig.
It's not as good as before, but it works.
You know, not bad.
I could add electric charge to this, but that would be a little scary as well.
Or I could add it.
Oh, wait, wait, wait.
Really?
Ha!
Electric rock.
I feel like that's a recipe for disaster.
Let's not do that.
But burning trail.
I feel like that's also a recipe for disaster.
Let's not do that.
Oh, my God.
Okay, I think we're good.
Let's just move on, huh?
Let's heal.
Doink!
I'm never going to need this spell refresh.
Because I'm always fresh.
So I'm going to get out of here.
Let me remove this.
I'm on fire!
Oh, wait, because the...
Oh, my God.
The rock is on fire.
There we go.
It's gone.
Can I get through here, please?
Hello.
There we go.
Wait a minute.
It wasn't here.
It triggered here.
Maybe it's like...
Maybe it's if you go above a certain height.
I don't know.
I'm trying to imagine in my mind what exactly is happening there.
Like from a game design perspective, really.
I'm trying to metagame this a little bit.
Okay, so I have a rock and I have a...
Well, a classic here that I had last time.
But I don't have enough mana, so I can't shoot this forever.
But it will kill enemies if I need to.
In fact, I'm going to put that on...
Yeah, it's actually fine.
I mean, see, that is doing work.
That is doing work.
It's killing enemies.
That's the issue with the rock, you know?
It does stuff like this.
I can't even cut it through.
Damn it.
The rock is good for open spaces.
Oh, I have this!
I forgot I have the telekinesis.
Look how much damage that did!
Oh my god, will you stop?
Oh, that's going to be annoying.
Stop it!
Only use the rock when there's this clear enemy that needs to...
Like, high value enemies that have a lot of HP, you know?
That's when I use it.
But until then, I'm just going to use my machine gun.
I mean, that's a classic.
It works.
If you shoot...
Oh, that hurt!
If you shoot it in short bursts, it's not that bad, you know?
Have a rock.
He's perfect for that sort of thing.
In fact, hold on, hold on.
Watch.
Okay, now watch.
Wait.
Dude, I can take this?
I can use the same rock again and again?
I just discovered a way to do this build without having unlimited spells.
You take one rock, and you just pick it up again.
Look!
And then you just walk around with it, and you go like, oh, you want this rock as well?
You know, then you just shoot it off.
Acceleration.
Neat.
Yeah, let's get in here.
I'm scared of using my... digging on that.
God damn, this rock is immense.
Hahaha!
Shit.
Oh my god.
I keep forgetting I have this wand.
Damn it, I missed the money.
Oh, shit.
Oh, the teleport bounces off this thing.
That is nuts.
By the way, I don't think I've ever died in this place, in this game.
I don't think I've ever died in this level.
It's like one of the easier levels.
This rock right here is wild.
It's really hungry for an enemy.
Whoops.
Come here.
Damn!
What was that just now?
Was that a small piece of the rock that still went around?
Give me this money.
So much fucking fire everywhere.
Hello!
He had a wand!
Decelerating shot, how about no?
That's a sweet wand though.
29 recharge though, that's a little on the low side, isn't it?
But 1400 max mana, oof.
Not bad.
Everyone dies.
You hear that sound over there?
That's one of my rocks going to town.
Just doing whatever it is rocks do.
Wish I could get through there.
This rock is eager to kill this dude over here, you see?
It's like magnetized.
Okay.
Boink!
What's that?
Freezing liquid, that's bad.
Don't want that.
What's this?
Oopsy daisy.
Boink!
You know what's cool about the rock?
It absorbs shots when it flies towards the enemy.
It counts as a physical object.
So right there, he was shooting towards me, but the rock absorbed the shots as it approached him.
Very cool.
Oh god,
that's way too much fire.
I got some of the money.
In fact, I don't know how I'm getting so much money.
I feel like I'm getting way more money this run than I usually do.
Uh-oh, that guy has a wand!
Ho!
He blew himself up, I think.
That is a thunder wand.
Sparkbolt with double trigger!
What?
I have never seen that!
It has more damage, I think.
Look, it is more damage.
Oh, that's exciting.
I kind of want that.
Maybe I'll say no to my teleport.
Hold on, do I have an extra teleport?
Fuck, why didn't I put my teleport up here?
I'm an idiot!
Come on, Rock, kill him.
Kill the extra dude up there as well.
I have to try this, I'm sorry.
Fuck teleport.
Double trigger sounds, completely nuts.
Gotta try that one.
Okay, uh...
Alright.
Doing!
I keep forgetting I have the telekinesis!
Wait, why is the...
What's in here?
Oh!
Healing bolt?
Dude.
Yes, yes.
Throw away that one.
Maybe I'll take...
explosion as well.
Thank you!
I will come again.
Actually, I won't.
But, you know, it's a nice thing to say.
Oh, that guy has other plans.
Good thing is, this rock also goes through this force field there.
Oh man, did they really want to get up here?
Alright, fine.
Sir, that's for you.
You want some of that?
Ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch.
Got him.
4,600, just casually doing that amount of damage.
Nice.
Slash explored.
Let's move on.
What was this one again?
The teleport, right?
I can always come back for it if I want, I guess.
I say that all the time and it never happens, of course.
Hey, look at this, there's a rock here.
Imagine just minding your own business, you know, you're hanging out in the heezy base, you know, taking a stroll.
Suddenly, someone's digging through the fucking roof.
You see just fire everywhere and this rock just comes down and flies towards you at magnificent speeds and you just get obliterated instantly.
And that was your day at work.
Feels bad, man.
Go!
Go, rock, go!
Or what's left of you, I guess.
Swoopity!
I love saying swoopity.
I just killed that guy with my thing.
Nice, we discovered the thing.
Oh, what is this?
Oh, that's the Anvil thing.
In fact, hold on, I want to try something.
Repair my wand.
Oh!
Magic arrow with timer.
It's a shuffle wand.
Fucking hell.
I need to experiment more.
Very nice, but I don't like any of this, honestly.
I mean, the wand is kind of sick, but it's a shuffle wand.
All right.
Maybe I'll just try it real quick.
Hold, that's scary.
Thank God there's no friendly fire on that.
How much damage does that do?
Ten.
Damn.
Look how long this wand is, dude.
Also, I never tried this.
Capacity 19 is sick, though.
Zero degree spread.
If I can just put a bunch of, well, of the same spell in here, it will shoot fast.
It even has a decelerating shot on it.
So that means what I'm seeing right here...
Wait.
What I'm seeing here is actually slow projectiles.
They could be even faster.
You know?
Magic arrow with timer.
No, I don't want it.
But I can't believe that fucking worked.
I need to try more stuff like that.
That's what I mean.
Just put random stuff on random stuff, you know?
Well, it wasn't that random.
I figured... animal, you know?
Can I repair it?
Can I bend it into place?
So I guess that makes sense.
Okay.
Let's go up.
Nice.
That was the teleport?
I feel like that's gotta be a secret that I just unlocked in my progress.
I can get through here.
Go.
Wait, I have been here.
Oh, wait.
No, no, no.
There's actually more.
Let's go around here like that.
Is that rock still at it?
This rock is really wanting to get through there.
Let's release the rock.
Ah, shit.
It's just murdering.
Look.
And it's done.
Good rock.
Such a good rock.
The best rock.
Can I use this to blow a hole in this wall?
Let's see.
Got enough power.
It is not.
Oh, well.
We tried.
All right.
I really want to get in here.
Look at all these enemies.
There's a chest as well.
Oh, shit.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Also, there's electricity up there.
That's scary.
Uh, I dare use a glowing lance in this.
If I do...
If I'm a little lucky here, I could maybe make a hole through.
Why is this glowing lance not making a hole?
It did last time.
But I think I also had speed up back then.
Let me in.
There's no way in.
Fuck.
All right, fine.
I'll come back later.
Damn.
This is the funniest weapon.
Look how crazy it is.
It just keeps killing.
It won't stop killing my
pet rock.
I feel like I should name the rock.
Maybe it's just Dwayne.
Keep it simple.
Dwayne Johnson.
So, what is this place?
Can I do anything in here?
Oh, my God.
Stop.
You're making so much noise.
A circium.
I'll take it.
This music is new, by the way.
This is...
I haven't heard this one before.
This is all new.
I'm on fire.
What is this place?
Oh, my God.
Stop.
Get him.
There we go.
Dude, I wonder.
If I telekinesis it...
I wonder if it actually does more damage, because I sort of give it a little push to begin with.
I didn't pay attention to the damage numbers.
But I bet it was a lot.
That fucker hit me.
I'm just so happy this rock doesn't hurt me.
That would actually make this build...
Whoa, what just happened there?
I'm stuck.
That was weird.
Look
at this one!
Yo, what's that ice ball?
Okay, let's try that.
Oh!
Releases that bullshit.
Okay.
How much damage?
Huh.
That's not bad.
Oh.
That is actually not bad.
Oh, my God.
Stop.
But I don't want it.
Not right now.
I also think that was shuffled.
Have fun in there.
I just said a rock lose.
It's the funniest thing.
I don't want that either.
Goddamn, son.
A chest.
Thank you.
Not that I need the money.
I have so much of it.
Sleeping quarters.
Can I lie down?
Can I do anything here?
Would you like some coal and soil in these trying times?
Maybe not.
Uh, let's get rid of that.
Makes it.
Ouch.
Scary animation on that rock.
Would there be anything more terrifying in real life than having a rock come flying towards you magically just homing on you?
Goddamn, that sounds absolutely horrific.
Reminds me of that one movie with Will Smith, where he's in the Wild West.
I think it's actually called Wild Wild West.
And they have these things...
Oh, God.
That's electricity!
Yeah, we're not doing that.
Nope.
Anyway, there was this thing in the movie where they were wearing these colors and they would send out these rotating blades that would cut off their heads because of the magnetism or something.
It was really dumb, but that shit scared me as a kid.
Reminds me a bit of this, you know?
Oh, my God!
I'm actually dying here.
Look at all these corpses!
I didn't even do anything over here.
Dwayne took care of all of this on his own.
Unstoppable killing machine.
What's this?
Oh, another one of these?
No, thanks.
Yo!
Did you see that guy?
He had a massive wand on him.
Wait a minute.
Let me see what's in here first.
Oh, be careful!
That thing's gonna explodey.
Okay.
Nothing here.
Let's go check out that wand.
Is he in here?
Sir?
I'm gonna let this rock lose on you.
No, you're up there.
There we go.
Oh, at mana!
Holy bomb!
Oh, I want this.
I want this.
Maybe I want this more than that, actually.
Yeah.
I want this more than that.
I found a new friend.
Unfortunately, that was shuffle again.
These shuffle wands everywhere.
Also a shuffle wand, but digging bolts.
Digging bolts, huh?
Yeah.
I mean, I want them all.
Honestly, I just can't have them all.
One of the tragedies in life.
You want it all, but you can't have it all.
Oh my god.
Oh my god, this rock is wild.
Is it that one making all the sound?
Also, I'm kind of low HP here.
Right.
I forgot about that heart completely.
Mix and match.
Go!
Do you think rock?
There we go.
Grab it.
Yeah.
In fact, I'm going to fill up my water bottle.
Oh my god, come on.
Nice.
I think it may be time for us to move on.
Low HP, lots of money.
That's usually the sign, you know?
Let's go.
Okay.
It's going pretty well.
Before I take anything, let's see here.
What the fuck is that?
Mana to damage.
I don't know what that means, but that sounds cool.
Let's see the perks.
More blood, no.
Projectile repulsion sector.
Protectiles that fly into a small sector in front of you get blown away.
How much blown away?
You gain two rand...
Oh, I am...
I'm actually tempted.
I could also do that.
But the thing is, if I do this, it's going to affect the next one too.
It's like a heavy investment every time you do, you know?
I feel like I should go crazy.
I'm not going to try this.
What did I get?
You bleed flammable oil, but I'm immune to fire.
You gain double the gold per nugget.
Bro, I'm already rich.
I don't need more money.
Holy shit.
Let's try this one then.
Oh wait, I need space.
Let's throw away some of these.
Oh, 20 only.
If the wand has more than 50 mana, all mana over that is converted into additional damage.
Only 20 users remaining.
So if I have a wand with like 1500 mana, you could do some crazy stuff.
You could put this on a spark bolt.
Dude, I understand why this is limited.
I understand.
Let's see what else.
Toxic sludge to...
Why would I want that?
That sounds horrible.
Essence to power.
What is that?
Increases a projectile's damage based on the number of creatures nearby.
I mean, that could be pretty good.
You know, if there's always creatures where you are when you're fighting, it's just a passive damage boost really.
I mean, it does cost a lot of mana, so that's the thing.
But look at this!
We have add mana!
I know where I'm putting that.
Oh, we're back, baby!
Look at that!
Let's see if we can make this even more crazy.
Let's see...
Ooh.
Holy shit, it's still not enough.
We need more mana.
But that is pretty dope.
I like it.
I like it a lot.
Ah, damn.
Maybe I put this one in here too.
Is that too much?
Probably is right.
110 mana drain?
Nah, that's not gonna work.
Reduce recharge time.
Is this gonna make things even more crazy?
I mean, it's already insanely fast.
Hold on, what if I were to remove this now?
Yikes.
Adding that little thing at the end.
Just completely changes everything.
Isn't that wild?
Look at that stuff.
What if I put this in here?
Whoa!
Wait, what?
It summoned a thundercloud?
Oh, oh, shit.
Oh, shit.
I saw water and I saw electricity and I got scared.
Brings bad luck to anyone it hits.
I see.
Let's try again.
Oh, God.
Yeah, we gotta get out of here.
The water's spreading.
Damn.
Uh, let's try another one.
Let's try...
Wait, magic missile?
This is infinite now.
And I am immune to fire.
Oh, my God!
Look how much damage I'm doing.
A thousand!
Wow.
Holy shit.
Let me see how accurate this is.
Is it drop off and stuff?
Let's see here.
Oh, my God.
I think I like it.
Freezing gaze.
Let's see what this is.
I think I had this one before.
A heart-freezing sinister aura.
Right.
Uh...
Let's get rid of these.
Right.
What if I put this here?
Oh, wow.
Let's see how much that does.
Two thousand five hundred damage.
I'm stuck.
Oh, it froze the water because it's freezing.
Oh, my God.
This is getting even more crazy by the minute.
I mean, I don't have enough mana for it, obviously.
That's nuts.
Let's try the magic arrow.
Oh, man.
Let's see how much this does.
It's not that great.
Let's be honest.
It's not fantastic.
Let's try some more stuff.
Let me do...
What about this?
Propane tank.
Oh, I don't have space.
Get rid of...
That.
Wait.
Homing propane?
No.
I mean, that's way too dangerous.
I'm going to kill myself with that.
Or not.
Oh, I can actually put homing on this.
Dude, wait a minute, wait a minute, wait a minute.
Oh, but I know I need the homing on the rock, though.
Right?
I was about to say we could put homing on...
Where is it?
This one.
But wait, it already is sort of homing, no?
Your spells home towards enemies very slightly.
Oh my god, the recoil on this is...
Kind of insane.
Maybe I shouldn't use this.
Oh my god.
I do like this one the most, I think.
Look how crazy that is.
That is just unbelievable.
That is wild.
I mean, we don't have enough mana to keep it sustained, but fuck that.
It does so much damage, dude.
We don't need that damage.
What is this?
A magical bolt with rejuvenated powers.
What?
So wait.
I can shoot myself?
Say what?
Hold on.
How can I utilize this?
So wait, I can heal an enemy?
Why would I do that?
Why would I heal an enemy?
That makes no sense.
Unless I can somehow...
I was about to say, maybe I can like...
Dude.
We found a spell that reduced the flight time of a projectile to zero, remember?
Maybe that will make it so it hits me right when I stand here.
You know?
But I forgot why that was cold.
But we found something like that.
Shit.
Was this bubbly bounce?
Okay.
I think...
This one is like a little promising in a way, but I don't understand how it works.
I think I'll put that on the back burner for a while.
What if I put this in here?
Is that gonna dig more?
Okay, what if I remove it?
I'm not sure.
I'm not sure if it's faster.
Let me...
I mean, it's shuffled and shit, right?
So...
It's completely random.
That is a modifier.
So if anything...
I mean, not that it matters, because it's...
What if I do put this into a non-shuffle one just to test?
Just to see here.
Yeah, I don't know.
We're just gonna keep it like this.
And this one we keep up here.
So before I move on, what I really want to do now is make sure I grab the spells and have them up here that I would like to use in the future.
You know, I think like this one is good.
I don't need multiple of these, I don't think.
At least just so I have one of each, you know?
Propane tank is like...
Maybe.
Although damage explosion 325, that is a sick amount of damage.
Someone's a propane tank.
Be careful what you wish for.
Indeed.
These are...
This one...
Put this up here.
That there.
And what should I make in this one?
Because this one is my cool new wand.
That's the cool new.
I could...
I could also put a flaming projectile on it.
Or like a modifier.
Be kind of sick.
Or I could just maybe be boring and do like that.
Oh, that's way too boring.
Also, I don't want this wand.
Where's my...
No, this is actually the only one I have.
What should I...
Maybe...
I'm not sure.
Maybe I want to be able to summon propane tanks.
Maybe the explosion from that can be useful somehow.
Or actually magic missile to dig.
Oh, it's really slow.
Holy shit.
Long cast a lay on that.
Plus one second.
Wow.
Wait, if I do this...
Okay, never mind.
Essence to power.
Oh, you know what?
Wait, this is technically a projectile.
How about we do this?
I mean, we're not going to be able to shoot rocks as fast.
But maybe it's worth it.
Let's see if that affects the damage at all.
Let's see here.
Whoa!
Yo, that looks cool as hell!
All right.
I think I got what I need.
Oh, you know what?
Let's grab a couple of these, I guess.
Yeah, that's good.
And in here...
Maybe I'll grab this one too.
Just a half.
And we're off.
Yeah, we're off.
Uh, this wand.
Let's do this.
Wait, is that infinite?
Oh my god!
No way!
The holy bomb is infinite!
Fuck yeah!
That's awesome.
Perfect.
That's all I want.
Yes, sir.
Holy shit.
Uh, what is that down there?
What the hell is that?
Die.
Oh, this wand.
Let's check it out.
It sounds nuts when you shoot it.
How far does it go, even?
It's like a huge shotgun, basically.
That's cool.
I have a rock for long distance and a shotty.
This is my clear out AOE spell, you know?
Very cool.
The rock is still just the best.
Let's see if the damage is different now that I have this modifier on it.
2004...
I mean, it's still just huge numbers.
Oh dude, I'm gonna find this boss again in here.
And fuck him up.
That was in here, no?
Uh, right side somewhere?
Let's find him and fuck him up.
Whoa.
Also, let me, uh...
Oh wait, I have to remember, I don't have explosion immunity now, so...
The holy bomb is gonna be...
But wait, I am fire immune.
That's one thing.
Let's see.
Definitely blows up somewhere and starts burning shit.
Let's just keep it in mind.
Only use it when we can get to safe distance.
That's like the rule.
Sup, man?
Did that just instantly kill everything that spawned out of him as well?
Oh, and the enemies dropped more gold now, right?
Because of the perk?
I'm gonna be super rich.
Oh my god.
Piss off.
Okay, so the rock doesn't do too much to these plants, unfortunately.
But this one does.
I have a wand for every occasion.
Oh, he does kill him when you hit him straight on.
Uh, shit.
Wait, block?
Oh, I'm blocking fire!
That's actually insane.
That's actually a big deal, I think.
Why are these flowers inside the brickwork?
What's happening?
Hello?
Excuse me?
Huh?
What?
The hell?
What is even going on?
Have fun.
Show them so much gold!
Uh, there's a worm.
I'm stuck!
Oh, I can't get out.
Oh, damn, I almost drowned.
I almost drowned in goo.
Oh, shit.
This is that bullshit liquid.
What the hell?
This worm has been doing some digging.
There's just gold falling from the sky because of Dwayne The Rock Johnson.
He's up there doing things.
Hello.
Yeah.
Hey, yo.
Look, notice how this rock is not super effective against the plants.
That works.
Sometimes it works like that.
Oh, my God, things are just dying.
I'm a force to be reckoned with here.
I wonder what the maximum damage is.
You can do in this game.
There's got to be ways to just break the system, right?
And make something completely broken.
I mean, like, I feel like I'm already up there, you know?
Like, the damage on this rock right here is insanity.
Oh, come on, die, please.
Just blast it away.
Okay, okay, this looks promising.
Are we close to the boss?
Dragon Cave.
That's it.
How dare you?
Oh, wait, wait, stand here.
Go up here.
Oh, my God, stop.
Where are you coming from?
Okay, that's it.
What is that?
Another worm!
Whoa, look at the statue.
There's something about the statue.
I can probably do something here.
Also, I'm very oily right now.
Oh, is it that thing up there?
I turned him into dust.
Jesus.
Let's go.
Watch this.
I'm gonna...
Let's see.
I'm gonna holy hand grenade.
Then when he comes out, I'm gonna fall.
Let's have a real detailed plan here.
I fall all the way down to, like, here.
And then we fight here.
What is that?
Protectile there.
Appearing.
Randomly.
Okay, that's the plan.
Let's go.
Jesus fucking Christ, that does a large explosion.
Is he gonna appear?
One more.
Come on.
Appear, appear.
I know you wanna.
Come on, bitch.
The rock is ready for you.
One more.
Oh.
Maybe I need to pee in here for him to spawn.
I'm scared.
There.
That should do it.
Come on.
Again.
Wake up!
What the fuck?
There we go, there we go, there we go, there we go.
Got him!
That was easy.
Blown away, bitch.
More teleport.
Double spell.
A thousand mana.
This is a sick looking...
What?
Actually.
Hello?
What's that?
Sawblade orbit?
Wait a minute.
Get rid of...
Get rid of that one.
Okay.
Makes four sawblades rotate around a projectile.
Hot damn.
How about we put that around the rock?
Not only did we let the rock lose on the enemies, but we also gave him a bunch of sawblades to have fun with.
How about that?
How about them apples?
Unless those sawblades will actually fuck me up, then that's a different story, you know?
Boink.
Can teleport now.
Fill up my water flask.
Always good to do.
These rocks are still...
So the fact that these rocks are doing this means there's enemies down here.
Yep.
Got him.
Do I want to go through yet?
No, I don't.
I want to find the spider lair.
And I'm gonna fuck those bitches up.
With the weaponry I found here?
Oh, I'm confident I can do some damage.
Hello?
Please die.
Oh my god, this rock is not done.
He's hungry.
He wants more.
I have 7k gold somehow.
This perk is wild.
Uh...
That's a mine.
Man, just being able to do this is actually wild.
Oh, here we go.
It's a spider.
Oh yeah, it instantly kills a spider.
That's awesome.
That's all I needed to know.
Fuck yeah.
Spiders are a good buy.
See ya.
Kill that thing.
Have fun with that.
Oh yeah?
Come on.
There we go.
There's something up there.
What is hiding up here?
Ah, another plant.
And then the rocks fall down.
Pretty neat, huh?
There's a rock somewhere.
Doing things.
It's like having a little dock with me that can sniff out enemies.
You're like, where are the enemies, boy?
Where are the enemies?
That way?
Okay.
Let's release the worm and kill the worm.
Ah.
So good.
Hold on, am I actually dissolving the gold that drops from those guys when I shoot it with this thing?
Is this even the spider area?
I'm not sure it is.
Why doesn't that break?
Oh, what's that?
Quadruple scatter.
Plasma beam orbit.
Makes four plasma beams rotate around a projectile.
How about we do saw blades and plasma beams around Dwayne Johnson?
How about them apples?
Maybe not, huh?
I feel like that would also be very dangerous.
Because I gotta be honest, I have my own well-being in mind as a first thing here.
Second comes killing enemies.
That is concentrated mana potion.
Awesome, I'll take it.
Where
are the enemies, boy?
I see one.
I feel like this one right here is the embodiment of the...
So anyway, I started blasting meme.
You know?
Hold on, is this gold being dissolved with this?
It's not, okay.
Just testing.
Health!
I mean, more health.
Bastard.
That's...
Oh, dude, I'm oiled all the time because I bleed oil.
Oh, that's scary looking.
Fuck me.
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on.
Jesus.
And now the rocks are loose.
What's that?
Ambiguous meat.
Let's eat it.
Oh, I'm confused.
35 seconds?
Oh, that's bad.
I think I'm gonna wait that out.
At least I know that what that does now.
Who would have thunk?
Don't eat ambiguous meat.
If it's ambiguous, a bad idea, you know?
Wait a minute, why is that blue?
Oh, okay, I thought it was electricity.
Jesus.
Let's wait for this to go away.
What's happening over here?
Oh, something's going on over there.
Wait, what's happening with my projectiles here?
Why is it all bending down like that?
What?
Is the gravitational field here really weird?
The hell?
The hell's going on?
Isn't that interesting?
Look at that.
Oh, wait, I understand.
They're homing towards the plant.
Jesus.
Uh-oh.
See ya.
Uh...
No.
No, thank you.
What is that up there?
Ow!
Wait, you're not dead.
Man, this fire protection is saving my ass.
Constantly.
What the hell is that?
You see that?
What?
Unfortunately, I can't get in.
I don't have the means.
What the fuck am I now?
I'm just digging.
Uh-oh.
I see you.
Have fun.
That's right.
Enjoy.
Why is he not killing a spider?
Dude, the spider takes no damage from the rock somehow.
Why is that?
That's not good.
That makes me unhappy.
Another statue.
I think I really like this oil perk.
Oh, that's the spot.
That's it.
This is it, boys.
Lukey lair.
Oh, here we go.
I can't even dig through this shit.
Oh my god, okay.
Rock, go kill enemies for me.
Is all this?
I can dig through this, at least.
Oh wait, that's a spider, isn't it?
Please tell me this rock will kill them.
Tell me it's damaging them.
Why is it...
They're not taking any damage.
What is it with these spiders?
Oh, I hate it.
Hopefully this thing will do the trick.
Oh, that's so fucked up.
Load all the legs.
Dude, the rock does nothing.
Oh, thank god.
Die, bitch.
Holy shit.
God damn.
Oh, my whole body is cramped.
Okay, at least this weapon is good.
Fucking spider guts.
Yikes.
Oh no, I have the bullshit liquid.
Water me, water me, water me.
Slime me.
Okay, that's fine.
Jesus.
Oh no!
Oh no, not those things.
It's actually ogre.
I totally forgot about those bullshit things.
How am I gonna release a rock, and hopefully it kills them?
But it's a fucking cloud.
Is a rock gonna hit a cloud?
That doesn't make any sense, right?
Hopefully this game doesn't make sense.
Come on, do something, rock.
Come on.
There, go.
Kill.
Get it, get it.
Yes!
It's killing.
Something on that side as well.
The hell is that?
Hook bolt!
A glowing hook that pulls cast towards itself upon collision.
Oh, like a teleport, actually, but a different...
type of teleport.
See, this would be nice with that spell I have that increases the damage based on the mana.
Wouldn't it?
That'd be really cool.
Come on, clouds.
Oh no, this is the liquid.
Don't stand on that.
Can I water that at all?
Doesn't seem like it.
What if I pour this stuff on it?
What if I pour...
Percircium.
Nope.
What about concentrated mana?
Okay.
Just testing.
It's all...
What the hell is going on here?
Hello?
What the...
Like, huh?
Oh, I can't even dig through that.
Everything's really dark here.
Nice.
We love that.
Come on, clouds.
Find an enemy for me.
I can't get through.
Here?
What is this material?
Lush ground.
Lush ground, apparently, is not able to be dug through.
But I can do this.
Almost.
It's almost working.
Actually, wait a minute.
Aha!
Oh yeah.
Oh yeah!
There's a wand down there.
Fuck you!
Oh, I just got a bunch of gold.
That's a lot of gold.
Yeah, got it.
Nice.
This area seems like a high risk, but high reward, you know?
Finding lots of these hearts here.
Oh, hello.
How about a rock in these trying times?
You appreciate that?
Jesus Christ.
That is a lot of gold.
Oh yeah, I'm not afraid of fire.
Something's blowing up up there.
What the hell is happening?
Bro, this fire immunity is actually wild!
I'm stuck!
Holy shit!
I'm almost dead.
Rock for you.
Dwayne, go!
Yup, yup, yup, yup, yup.
Wizards, then?
Yo, what?
It feels...
Okay.
Here's the plan.
I'm gonna nope out of here.
We're moving on.
I will come back here later in this run, and check out the Wizards, then, because that sounds freaking awesome.
We're noping the fuck out of here right now.
We've had enough.
Plate safe.
Meticulous on the way out.
No bullshit, come on.
We gotta go right, basically.
Oh, wait, we haven't been here.
Let me grab this, actually.
Oh, man!
Jesus!
Holy crap, they came quick!
And that's not what she said.
Oh, wait, why am I going that way?
Don't go that way where the spiders came from.
Terrible idea.
Let's, uh, go this way.
I think, actually, that's where I came from.
I've been...
I dug this.
I did that.
Another spider?
Oh, they're so creepy looking.
I hate them.
Hey, guys?
You like that?
How about that?
Where did I come from?
Do I want to check this?
Let's check it.
Oh, I have been here.
Okay, okay.
So we go right.
Keep going right.
Ah, rest.
Are we making it out?
The spider behind us.
Oh, thank God.
Okay.
That was a lot of excitement.
Now we're going down to the portal.
If I can.
Oh, yeah, I can dig through this.
I'm just going down.
Fuck everything.
I have 14k gold.
What?
I've never had this much.
This perk is nuts.
I'm a rich man.
Here we are.
Let's just go.
No hesitation.
Jump in.
Jump the fuck in.
Hello?
You're not welcome here.
The fuck are you doing?
Yeah, that's right.
Get the fuck out of here.
Anyone else?
Cruisin' for a bruisin'?
Huh?
Who else?
There's poison here.
Actually, it's toxic sludge.
Let's remove that.
There we go.
What do we have here?
Toxic immunity.
Yo.
Cordyceps.
Concentrated spells.
Yo, concentrated spells with this?
Oh, that would be sick, wouldn't it?
Dude.
If that works on this, though, that's the thing.
Because this one doesn't actually have a spread on it.
So that's what's...
Oh, hold on.
There's an enemy.
Oh, that works.
That works.
Thank you.
Let's get rid of these rocks.
There we go.
Off we go.
Man.
I kind of want to re-roll.
Is that crazy?
Toxic immunity is awesome.
But does that work against acid?
It says toxic sludge and other toxic things.
Toxic is not the same as corrosive, but in my mind it sort of is, you know what I mean?
I'm not trusting it.
I'm re-rolling.
Contact damage.
Enemies near you take damage.
Damages higher the lower your health gets.
No.
Tinkled with wands everywhere.
A divine blessing allows you to tinkle with wands everywhere!
Yoink.
I'm taking that.
Fuck yeah, bitch.
Okay.
That's actually pretty cool.
Yo, this wand though.
Ah, spells per cast two.
Point seventeen.
Uh, what is that?
The fuck is that?
I mean, I'm so rich anyway.
I don't even care, buy it.
Uh, here.
Let's throw this stuff down here.
There.
Saw blade orbit.
Oh man, should I try?
Should I try?
That sounds scary.
But this damage field gives the projectile and energy field that constant deals 3.5 damage to nearby creatures.
Nah.
Magic arrow with trigger.
Let's try that one.
Does that do a big difference?
Or make a big difference?
You know what, that's not bad.
But, uh, I mean, come on.
This one.
Now that one is what I'm talking about.
You know?
That one is something else.
That's a crazy combination, man.
That's a sick wand.
Okay.
This wand though, point fifteen, point eight two.
It's actually not a great wand.
No.
I don't enjoy this wand.
Uh, this rock over here is annoying me.
Sounds like it's playing mahjong.
I'll probably push for that name for that game.
Let's see here.
What else do we have?
It's a good wand.
Uh, point zero eight.
It's all fucking two per and shuffle.
God damn it.
Spells per cast is two.
Point oh five.
Point two three.
This is actually a decent one.
Except there's only a couple slots, right?
That's the bad thing about that one.
But it's probably better for this.
Three seventy, one oh three.
What is this?
Five hundred.
Yo.
Spells ca- you know, let's try that.
What if we just put this down here?
So it shoots two spells per cast.
That's the confusing part.
So it's actually- I don't think that's going to change anything.
This is still just one spell.
Yeah, but the difference is I can shoot way more if I want to.
Pretty neat.
Uh, yeah.
Okay, these can stay there.
That's fine.
You can hang out over there, Dwayne.
It's okay.
This though.
Thunder charge.
Now that is cool.
I do like that.
Let's try it.
Uh, here.
Let's put this here.
And let's do this.
Let's try that one.
Hopefully it won't kill myself here.
I'm standing on water.
That's a little bit.
Forty five.
Oh!
Oh wait, I'm breaking the brickwork.
Hopefully the gods are not going to get angry.
I'm not actually going to do this anymore.
I'm scared.
Put it back.
I like how it was.
What if I put a heavy spread there?
What happens then?
You know what?
That's kind of a crazy oh shit button, you know, if you're surrounded.
Let's see what else I have.
Burst of air.
Oh, you know what?
I have an idea.
Burst of air.
What if we do this?
Oh no, wait, it's not a modifier, never mind.
I was going to say, if we can turn the healing bolt into a burst of air, maybe we can walk into it, you know, but it's not a modifier.
It's actually just a projectile.
Boink!
You know what?
I'm going to keep one of these.
They seem cool.
Now this wand is actually...
Do I want it?
I mean, I got to take this for a second here.
And at least have a teleport up there on the bar.
Let's not do the heavy spread.
And let's not do the spark bolts.
Let's not do that either.
Or that.
I'm gonna use one of these there.
We can remove some of these.
We don't need all of them.
The reduce recharge time.
See, this wand right here is actually a good wand.
That is a crazy good wand!
Let me try and put this stuff up here just to see.
What happens then?
Oh, I can shoot that for way longer.
Way longer.
And it charges quick as well.
Look at that.
That's decent.
How much damage?
It still does a lot.
I would say that's a success.
That is a success wand right there.
Because there's more space, we can even go more nuts here.
What if we just... let's have some fun.
Instead of a triple, how about we put a double inside of the triple?
So that means instead of doing pop, pop, I do this one and then we add another one.
Like... I don't even know.
That?
And another one of these?
What happens then?
I mean, that's nuts.
Let's see.
I can't even tell.
It's so weird.
No, that's too weird.
But it definitely works.
Let's put this back.
What if I add this somewhere else?
Then it goes on the... that's so interesting.
Whoa!
Yo!
Look at that.
Word impacts.
It releases that bullshit.
Because the freezing gaze is done where this impacts.
Actually insane.
Isn't it?
Isn't that actually wild?
Let
me see.
Let me see how this works over here.
I need a better test of long range.
I mean, that... it's doing some damage, right?
But I do like the idea of having a big area of effect that just fucks things up.
I think I'm just gonna stick with that.
You know?
Don't break if it's... don't break it if it's working, you know?
It's super good.
Look at the amount of damage that does.
I do wonder if I can put just something a little extra inside, you know?
Ooh!
Maybe this.
Oh!
I mean, if I'm doing this as an AOE spell anyway...
I mean, I run out of mana much quicker.
That's the thing.
So it's not actually that good, unfortunately.
Yeah, that's good.
We can spam that for a while.
And then we have this one down here we can utilize for things.
How about we make it one of these?
Oh, no, wait.
This is a... this one has a thousand mana.
No, let's not use this yet.
We're gonna use this when we find a wand with a sick amount of mana on it.
Do we just keep going for this?
No, wait.
We need a teleport.
This is gonna be teleport, of course.
Teleport.
There we go.
Teleport!
And that seems good.
Actually, I do want to try something real quick.
Let me try that one.
What's this?
Earthquake Shot.
Makes a projectile crumble the earth it hits.
Ooh!
Hold on.
Uh... I'm afraid of this one, though.
Because... will that anger the gods?
Yeah, I don't know about that one, dude.
Let's wait with that.
I'm scared.
Oh, wait.
We can tinker with stuff everywhere.
That's insane.
Let's just try that later, then.
Quadruple Scatter Spell.
Let's try that in here.
This is gonna be wild, isn't it?
It seems more violent, but it actually...
it doesn't do much more damage.
I can't even see the damage in all this.
1900.
Nah.
This is still the best.
Wait, did I break it?
It no longer shows me damage.
I must have broken it.
I'm sorry.
Actually, let me get some water.
Oh, wait a minute.
Actually, hold on.
Dude, I just had an idea.
What if we tried this?
What would that look like?
Oh, hold on.
Hold on now.
Oh, yo!
Let's see.
I want to see the damage, though.
Wait a minute.
Wait, wait, wait.
How much damage?
Oh, man.
It's not even that much.
The other one is way better.
It just seemed more violent, didn't it?
Maybe it's the sound.
Yeah.
Okay, so here's the thing.
When I leave here, I can still tinker.
Right?
Oh my... I can... I can hot-swap shit.
Oh, bro.
This perk is unreal good.
It's actually one of the best perks.
What the fuck is that thing up there?
Whoa!
Uh, hold on.
I'm immune to fire, but I'm not immune to toxicity.
Which means I shouldn't play Dota.
I still do it anyway, though.
Go this way.
Kill them all.
Get them.
Bro, call me crazy, but I feel like my wand right here is even crazier than the one I had in the last run.
And I thought that was crazy.
The only thing is, I don't really have any good means of digging.
I can't get through that, you know?
And that wand looks sick.
Oh, I could do this, I guess.
To get through here.
That's something.
I'm still scared, though.
Uh-oh.
Damn.
Water me, water me.
The difference between this run and the last is that I had way more HP last time.
Because I had a perk that increased the amount of stuff I would get every time I picked up a heart.
Uh, no.
Dude, I can find a wand, see a spell I like, and just instantly hot-swap it.
The freedom in that sounds incredible.
Oh, oh, oh, oh!
I guess he can't hit me anymore because of the rockets in the way.
Kill him!
Oh my god, rocks, come on, what's happening?
You're disappointing me.
This guy is completely fucked.
Can I hit him through the wall?
No.
My dude, he's gonna kill me, isn't he?
I'm slowly hitting him.
He's in an annoying spot.
God damn.
What's this?
Vacuum bounce.
Makes a projectile remove earth as it bounces.
Hold on.
Hold on a second now.
If I, oh my god, I'm so slippery!
Stand still.
Uh, let's say I do this one here.
Actually, put it here.
I don't know if that's better.
It's probably not, right?
No, because it's only, I only cast one spell anyway on this, so it's, if I had three of these freezing gazes, that would be the tits.
Although...
Wait a minute, wait, wait, wait.
Let's try this one now.
Let me remove this.
Oh my god, stop slipping all the time.
Uh, put that here.
Remove that.
Jesus!
Wow!
Okay, that's a powerful spell.
Holy crap!
Yo!
Earthquake shot, huh?
That is amazing.
Wow.
That shit doesn't fuck around.
I'm scared of that now.
Now, vacuum bounce.
Let's try that.
Uh, oh!
The digging is real!
No way!
We don't need this wand at all.
Fuck this wand.
Fuck the smoke.
Fuck that.
Everything gets fucked.
Away you go.
Uh, away you go.
Oh my god.
Oh wait, actually, I have an idea, I have an idea.
Hold on, don't throw that away.
I just had an idea.
What if we were to do this instead?
Uh, because if we can affect... This is a projectile, right?
Oh wait, it's limited use.
Oh no.
Dreams are ruined.
God damn it.
Mm, that's sad.
Wait a minute, where's the other one that makes Earth crumble?
Yeah, I don't know if I want to do this, because this hurt me just now, because the Earth fell on me.
That's bad.
We don't want that.
But, watch this.
What if I... Where'd that thing go I just dropped here?
Uh, throw that away.
Give me that.
What if I can make a digging wand?
So hold on.
Hold on now.
This is a projectile.
Um, what if I do something like... Oh wait, this is a shuffled wand though.
Hold on, I need to find the wand that is not shuffled.
This one maybe.
Oh yeah, that's my teleport wand.
Um, I actually need that back.
Let's put this here for now.
Let's throw this away.
I don't okay.
Now, uh, we throw this one away as well.
Grab that.
Maybe I say fuck teleport for now, because I can always put it back when I need it.
That's the crazy thing.
I do a double, right?
And inside of this, I put...
Um, inside of that, I put a... Let's say I put that, that, and that.
And then...
No wait, uh, one, two... That's a double.
Let's do another double.
Let's do it.
Do that.
So this one casts two, and this is one of them.
And this one contains digging, right?
Uh, digging.
And then I want maybe... Where's this thing I... Maybe actually this one.
Let me just try with the smoke.
Smoke?
I have, I have no idea.
Let's see.
Is that digging?
Oh, oh wow!
Oh wait, I'm burning myself though.
Why is that burning me?
Burst of air is weird.
Let me try this one.
Wait, does it even... Oh!
Wait a minute.
It's way more efficient.
Oh, this is not the one I thought I picked up.
Uh, wait a minute.
Where's that shotgun thingy?
Where did I leave that?
Shit, I don't know.
Oh, here, here.
Let's see this one.
Is it just me, or is this way more efficient now?
What did I do?
Did this, did this really do all that?
Hold on.
I guess it did.
Oh, it wasn't this one before, right?
Now it's in here.
And we made it more efficient by doing this stuff.
Oh, this is a way better digging one now.
The only issue is we can't get through hard material, right?
So we need to find a solution to that.
Here, we can put that.
That's our teleport.
Is this still the same?
I think it is, right?
We had that, that, this, that, that.
Hold on a second.
I'm, uh, not quite sure here.
This is what we had.
Six damage, damage ice 10.
Ah, it's fine.
Let's just move on.
This seems good.
teleport, and we have to dig.
It's way better now.
We just gotta keep an eye out for, uh, spells that can dig through hard material, basically.
But I have to say the main objective we have now is to actually find more HP.
Whoa.
Hello.
Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, hello, hello, hello, hello.
What the fuck was that?
Oh, it's one of these things.
Yeah, this place is dangerous.
Oops, toxic stuff.
Not good.
You know how you know it's acid when it eats through things.
Isn't that smart?
High level thoughts here only.
Yo.
Minus 0.03.
Maybe I'll just try that.
What is that?
Toxic mist?
No, remove that.
Nobody wants that.
So if I put in this now here, that's just, I could have...
Yeah, that's fine.
I just want this one more.
It's a better one in general.
It's also non-shuffle, so not that it matters, but the teleport is just a matter of principle.
Ah, shit.
Ah, no, we're fine.
Fine.
There's a wand up there.
What is that thing?
Runestone of magma.
What?
Wow.
Do I...
I want to pick it up.
Let's get rid of this fucking coal and barren soil.
I have no idea what the point of that is yet.
Let's just grab this now.
A runestone with a strong magical aura.
You feel like kicking it.
No, I feel like putting it on an altar somewhere.
Or maybe on the... putting it on the anvil, maybe.
Even though it doesn't make too much sense logically.
Summon hollow egg?
No.
I think the summon hollow egg is a spell I don't quite understand.
Look at that!
A shiny orb.
Did I just destroy that shiny orb?
Whoops.
I mean, not that I need money, but still.
Can't get through there.
Give me a plasma cutter.
And I say that with a bit of hesitation, because I tend to kill myself with that.
So maybe don't give me one of those.
Give me a black hole.
That is infinite, you know?
That's what I really want.
Infinite black holes.
Whoa.
Nice.
Sweet.
Look at all the money.
It's raining money.
Is that?
It is.
Oh wait, I've been here before.
I remember this exact spot.
What is that?
Kiva ski?
Why does that look like that?
Wait a minute.
Kill that guy?
Uh, get rid of the circuit.
Yeah.
I'm gonna try and put these things on the altars.
See what happens.
Anything that I can pick up, basically.
Oh, but you know what?
I can technically pick up all kinds of things now that I have telekinesis.
I could try to put all kinds of things on the altar.
Maybe that's like a little secret, you know?
Things you normally couldn't pick up.
But now you can with the telekinesis.
Maybe that will do something.
Uh-oh.
Don't fall down there.
I was kind of expecting there to be like a heart there or something, you know?
In the center of the acid.
I'm angry now.
Angry.
I'm going berserk.
Wait, did everyone die here?
Oh, I guess my rock must have done some damage.
Uh, that's a plasma cutter, actually.
Wait, can I hold on to this?
Oh, okay.
Bye-bye.
The hell is that?
Homebringer?
Water trail.
The wand looks really cool.
Visually.
Well, that's about it.
Bye-bye.
I think it's a soon time to go up again to the surface.
Uh,
where are you?
Oh, it's from the left.
That bamboozled me.
Wait a minute.
Is this doing way less damage than normal?
Hold on.
Did I change my wand in a way that I didn't intend?
Oh, that is doing no damage.
What the fuck did I change?
I changed something about this wand.
Uh, let's see here.
What did I do?
I did feel like there was a difference.
Whoops.
Shit.
Don't slip!
Oh my god, I'm filled with oil.
Stand still.
Let's see here.
What did I do?
What did I change?
Cast three... maybe I had a double here?
Is that the difference?
Oh, that looks different.
Look at that.
Let me see it with the triple again.
Oh yeah, that's way slower, isn't it?
Is it not?
Maybe not.
I'm not sure.
I'm gonna have to try that in the holy mountain.
But like, this is not doing nearly the same amount of damage.
Oh, but you know what?
Actually, I'm gonna stop here anyway.
It's actually seven o'clock.
I need to eat something and then I have to do something after that.
Man, I'm gonna exit right here in a very perilous spot.
I'm not gonna have much time to chat.
I'm sorry.
I went a little over time here.
That's what happens when you play this game.
Cheers, everybody.
I just want to say thank you to all the people watching and for subscribing and just chatting and hanging out.
It's really cool.
I'm sorry there wasn't much interactivity today with this, but next time I promise I'm gonna set off some time for that.
And then I'm gonna go to the surface and we're gonna solve some goddamn secrets.
It's gonna be good because I feel like I'm powerful enough to do crazy things.
So I'm gonna be out of here.
Thank you for watching.
I'll see you in the next.
Also, I'm gonna put up a Prey episode now.
So if you're watching that series, here it comes.
Have a good one.